This is Psychee Awakens, crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack, yo welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce get told, he goes unfold, we stir the soul with the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of
in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringing love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Sly for your wake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Sly for your wake, can't stop look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Hello, hey guys, what's up?
How'd you like that one?
Hi, he went to vampire girl. I'm a Levi's in on YouTube. You can go check her out. She's on almost every night
Tell her hi for me, but you probably can't because my name is blocking her chat, but
Good luck with that
Good luck with that. Oh Fred, I'm scared. I'm scared Fred. Wow
i'm really scared this guy fred is obsessed with me guys obsessed
here's hard lemonade what's up guys keep it up i'm asking for
sad people hey guys what's up guys look at my room so how clean it is i even have my table
Look see my whole place. He's my stairs to I have stairs
Hold on I prove it to you
There you go there's
Hi guys, I hope I was giving the inside scoop on everything my old mod KZ was never a mod
He's just a pathetic person. Thank you. Bye. Yeah, bye
Yeah, right is the
But we're doing a popcorn ceiling. Yeah, it's kind of pop for me. I do
Unfortunately lava is Fred. Oh
Wow, well look we gotta have a shower hold on shit
Hi, how are we doing tonight guys? I thought I'd come say hi hang out for a little while
Um, yeah, my coffee is a little bit cold. I got some hard lemonade still have that I can hold up
Just shut this
Unfortunately Fred, you won't be able to talk about me
because my name is blocked in the chat, in her chat.
So I can't even comment in her chat.
So what are you talking about?
You'll never hear about me again.
That's fine with me.
Can you block too?
Hey guys, hopefully this is like here.
How's that look?
I'm looking down a little bit.
Hey, what's up?
I do have the best chat, but the guys here look you can see the rest of my room
I know I never never should never show you really anything but here there's that room
You see a little bit my alien
This is my my bait
Linker
That's tricks, that's Mr. Tricks. Hey tricks
Tricks, come on
one tricks
here
Is everyone at Sam as bad? I was looking at Sam man's and it was cool Sam and as a good show
He was a Boston strong. How are you doing Boston strong as a member any other members Jamie's Cowboys and the member
Katrina's a member
Samantha Avery is the mod.
Look at it, we got a lot of members in here.
Congratulations on being,
a lot of you did with memberships here.
Hi.
Thank you for everyone who renews their membership
and enjoys the membership.
I do have a lot of content.
I do have extra long readings for the members.
And I will have like a, I think one day a week,
a just a members only.
I'll probably do it Sundays, I think, maybe Sundays.
I'll do like an hour just members and this you know talk about anything
Everyone would you?
So I think I'm looking pretty good lately
About your system football Jamie. Hi Boston strong
Yeah, how are you feeling Jamie? I know
Not been easy lately
Hey guys, if you want to check out I have this influencer page. It's not
I don't have anything on it yet
But I will start putting my products that I have from Amazon on it things that I bought or give been gifted to me
It makes me bookmark that page. That's my influencer page on Amazon also
Just apply for an influencer on Amazon if you have your own channel or anything because then you can get some
commissions and affiliate
You know some affiliate kickdowns for Amazon. So that'd be awesome, right?
What else do I need? I think I'll be able to get my computer this week
That's like one of the number one things also probably my bike fixed if it hasn't been fixed yet
My neighbor also is gonna fix it for me
One second done. Wow
What's next? I will have motorcycle you just asked me in discord. He was a mod
Yeah, he was a mod of maybe one point, but he was unmodded and he was kicked out, but
Whatever just bring my name up in discord. She loves it. She loves hearing more about me
You know, just just make me a bigger voice. Thank you so much Fred. Just keep mentioning me in her discord
I hope it doesn't get back to her up. Just contact me in a nice way
Because I've always been respectful. I made a little parody song a little love song. Is there anything wrong with that?
Am I doing something wrong?
Is it wrong to like feel like a scorned a
Not lover, but I did love her you gotta work your whoops
Yep, Samantha knows Samantha knows. I was also her first member
Our first member I
Remember my first members. I'm not I wasn't allowed. I'm not allowed who is this law tell me not allowed
I never heard once I wasn't allowed to talk about anybody.
I'm allowed to talk about anybody.
I want to call freedom of speech in America.
Are you from some like country
that doesn't have freedom of speech Fred?
How are you even allowed to watch her?
Guys, I did,
I did have a few free panels this week,
and so I am gonna do a sponsor panel tonight,
but the good news is it's $5 tonight
because School of Athens did donate $5 earlier,
and so I'm gonna count that towards opening the panel.
So if you'd like to cash out to have an advertisement
for a few hours and sponsor the panel,
you'll be the hero of the night.
Consent here.
But you can send us $10 or $5. However, we'd like to help the channel. It's very much appreciated
Gosh, I got some cigarettes. I feel pretty good today though because I really like I can't wait to show you guys my bedroom
I just have to clean it still as I like I have all my laundry in there on the bed right now
The bed's not made but once I make the bed and put away some stuff
Thank you. Hey guys, hopefully you guys are having fun on this show, too
I think this is a good show not a huge fan of his voice though
The band is tight which better you're talking about. Let's see you're talking about
Boston oh Boston the band Boston
All right, I'm thinking of Kansas thinking of Kansas, right?
Anyway guys
Yeah, so pretty excited though this month, you know some really amazing donations. Oh my gosh. Thank you so much
Arbitra Crucible Ghosts
Made my month
My first month over a thousand dollars on YouTube
You know guys I've been like pretty much unemployed for like the last
and I've tried so many things, so many things.
I mean, even like, some things have been successful.
Like I did my terror reading on Etsy was successful,
but it kinda like, I didn't keep up with the times really
and I was doing typed out readings.
This is like 2020.
All this and everything went to video
and I was like a little bit shy to go on YouTube,
but I knew I was like, oh, YouTube's the next thing
I gotta do.
And I got to be successful on it and I was like how is that gonna happen? I was like people are gonna like me
I'm not good looking enough. I'm not like interesting enough. I'm like blah blah blah. I
Had all these doubts, but things just worked out and like they think they were supposed to and
Now I have a show I have an audience at least 13 people in chat right now, you know
Sometimes they have to 50 people in chat, right?
And probably will tonight. I bet you let's get to 50 people in chat tonight. Can you everyone share like this live?
Let's have a fun night tonight
Just like a kind of celebratory mood
Scott step. So what's the last concert I went to? Hmm?
Last concert
Not Marilyn Manson it was just a long time ago
Long time ago
Oh, no, no, it wasn't that long ago. It was actually it was actually front row at
Or a third row it was like row C or row D at
King Diamond
Actually met this guy named hell Walker on Emma's show
And we became such good friends, like they actually came from San Diego, picked me up one night and drove me down to this VIP concert like front row, like it's like basically like it's like the most awesome thing it was like it was so cool.
We set up front of King Diamond who's like I think he's from Denmark and he's like probably in his 70s now but he had a really cool he was like probably before Marilyn Manson.
And then we got to meet King Diamond at the end of it, and you know if you get a picture taken I have that still
It's not one of my private videos. I think
But then right after that concert
But I had a falling out with that guy and that was like the start of a lot of falling outs
And some of the falling outs I've fallen back in with them
You know
A lot of people don't talk to me anymore.
This process is interesting.
Oh, you took your son to see King Diamond, Katrina?
That's so cool.
When did you do that?
You dropped me in the Gip of you flicking densely
from the floor of this court.
It's okay.
I think she might get a kick out of that.
But you know what, I do vacuum.
You can tell Emma I got a new vacuum cleaner.
And so I do vacuum up the dead fleas.
But yeah, I like to like kind of like crush the fleas
in my fingers and like flick them on the floor.
No.
Is it wrong?
I like seeing the dead fleas bodies kind of like stick.
No.
Move around a little bit before they stop. I hate fleas. I hate fleas. I have cats
Okay, the cats the fleas will actually like tricks of the allergic to fleas
I think he gets all bumpy and shit like that. It's like it's like my it's mad maddening
I'm a I'm immune to fleas and they don't like I can have like
Them all over me and I would not get bitten once or anything like that, but they they fucking bother the cats and
I'm happy to
That's awesome Katrina. I'm glad that he got to see King Diamond. So yeah, I got to see like it was like the mental asylum
kind of themed
Concert and we were right up like the probably third row. We got a bag of merch. I have a I have these dice
I do some some divination on dice. I want to do soon. It's called. It's called mo and it's from
It's called Moe and you like roll five dice and then it'll come to a number and then the number means something basically a Moe
But it's in form of divination and like you know, I studied to bed Buddhism under a llama
Oh, yeah, so Jamie I Lenore came in today for a while and she was and then she's like she was she went outside
She's the neighbor's backyard like stunning all day. She does the sun. I don't know. She's there right now. Let me check if she's there
She is I'll take you to take you guys over
Okay, that her no, that's not her
No, I
Promise Lenore's here. Lenore's likes to be outside right now. There's tricks right there tricks you're over there. Hi. I miss your tricks
Anyway guys, yeah
You got to see the third row and slayer clothes. Wow. Yeah, I forgot to the opening band was
for King and Diamond, but there were a couple good bands that I see the new picture and this board you made
I'm gonna check it out Jamie
Wish I had like, you know, it was easier to like communicate like pictures and stuff with people like but I guess like you know
There's for a lot of porn or something like that if people were able to put pictures up so easily, you know, but
I mean, I like sharing, I love how I'm able to share stuff like, but on TikTok, it's kind of like even better than this, like, or it's like, you can like, have like,
put words on the screen without like, being on YouTube, so I'll show you some of my things, like, this is like the...
Some like prototype, uh, there's I'm not gonna use that but I kind of was like be the like laughing and like me like starting out like
Oh, I'm gonna try to do a YouTube show. I just have a bunch of cats and then it's like it was like crazy
I just stepping into I don't know what I'm stepping into like, you know my future and then I turned into the magician
There's like one more and then I had beta and the Empress
That was kind of page as the high priestess
I tried me as a devil this one kind of like came out a little bit scary and then this one too
I liked how that looks a little bit better. This was like one of the newer
Magician and then there was even that went after that. So I made a bit. I've here. Oh, there's Jamie. I'm sorry Jamie
I'm I just leave these home
Is there on those?
They just take these off. I'm so sorry. Hold on. Sorry Jamie. Hold on
Lee lead
We'll take off Lucifer
Oh, yeah, let's see this alley like I mean some things that aren't like really useful like this is useful
I love this cat right here. That's useful. I don't have third eye Thursday
Maybe I just we have the banner for this let me check once again
Third eye Thursday I
Do I do hold on right here?
Can add this
Do you guys like the banner for this episode? I'll take down the end this up
That was like probably the last time I'm gonna play that song. I think I got the point across and
Yeah, how's that one that's pretty huh I made this on Canva there you go guys, how does that look?
Canva is pretty damn cool. I would say you know if you were looking to do graphics
You know, I would say you can look pretty professional
Canva also has an AI. I think I made this with the canva AI just saying hey make it third
I Thursday like a psychedelic kind of looking thing like you know
It kind of knows you my style that I like purple and stuff like that and it's just the perfect job. So that's canva
You guys want a link I could probably do like a link or something to it like I wonder if I can promote it
Let me see hold on one second
Yeah, it would have been cool if they had like actually like a
It was hey, okay, so how are you guys? Hey time? How are you doing? How's everybody doing tonight?
Yeah, so I'm getting a little bit drunk tonight
I only have three drinks though, and I have a they finished my burger yet finish my burger and finish
I still have like half as hard a little bit. Okay drunk tonight. Hey, what's up sukey make walkie?
How did you find the show awesome? Where you from?
You sound interesting and nice looking guy here. Look at this guy. Hi
Welcome to the show
Yes, I'm mr. Psychi. Well, that's what uh, that's what you me calls me
Do you know you me from Indonesia? She calls me mr. Psychi mr. Psychi
It's really cute. I don't mean to be a fence. I'm sorry. Hi guys. How are we doing tonight? Yeah?
I feel really good right now because you know, I've cleaned up my
My house a lot and it's like so much like junk has like gotten cleared away like I vacuum with new vacuum. Hi guys
So, let me finish up this beer and we'll have a conversation. I'll bring some carts over soon and stuff
over fun a little fun night
We're gonna have a panel too. I mean people can come up one at a time right now
I do want to get like a five dollar donation before I do open the panel as an open panel
Because I got a five dollar donation earlier. Thank you school of Athens for the five dollars earlier
I don't make sure at least make ten bucks a day on the show. They could you know
If I made ten dollars a day, which is like, you know
This at least that at least be like 300 bucks a month. That'll keep me going the show, you know, no matter what you send me a DM
Okay, thank you Momo. Um, yeah, you're on a on tripped
Tick-tock
How's my day?
I'm having a great day Boston strong. How are you doing? How I need to bring this closer because
There we go. Make a call. Okay. Let me just put
I have so yeah, I used to have a tripod, but now I have like a stand
So it's a little bit
Like I'm looking down like hey, what's up? I don't need to like well. I want to like look friendly
That but then I can't see now, but I can kind of like read better
I can still read it that kind of me closer
My vision is going all wonky. Yeah, so I was enjoying like Sam and show like but I mean
It was like it got it a lot into like the beat of Jim Nick
Saga and it was just like a little bit like much, you know
Like I guess real friends will like always be real friends. I'm like, you know, if you're not if you're not then it's like I guess we'll like
fall apart, but it's like I think like
Sometimes arguing makes things better sometime. I love makes things like stronger. I mean I'm better. I mean it's like better to like
work through arguments and have had the arguments rather than like, you know always have like
some kind of like
Unsaid thing. I think we're hanging in there. Just hanging in there be respectful to everybody in the chat
Oh, thank you. You know, I think the chats would be respectful. We did have that like Joker Fred
Fred is here like I'm being a flying monkey for Emma or whatever or like
You know Casey has gone to that chat and he thinks he's like gonna humiliate me by sharing all about my show and like
I'll be embarrassing things maybe that I've done in on my show in that that discord and like they can all laugh at me or
Whatever, but you know what they don't know any of the truth. They don't want even watch the show
And so how would like what does he even know they just have little flying monkey Casey go over there?
You know
Okay, and I probably even unblocked
Unblocked it. Yeah, it was like nobody liked him on the show
And then it was like then he'd like the system like being here for the whole show and stuff
And then like, you know, I don't really don't kick people off. He's just like kind of sit in the background like and you hear like the bad like
Sound, you know, it would like and then he was just like in his microphone burp and stuff and then like
I started doing my like, you know, just one at a time thing and he just couldn't understand like the concept of like, you know
I'm just gonna have one at a time until
Until the panel gets sponsored and then he's never donated a penny and so what I didn't have him on and so he gets so mad
He goes over to her chat and the talk about shit because he knows, you know
She doesn't probably like me very much and like, you know, it's so easy to smear me. No one ever goes to the store
So it's like they always just like we'll like
Oh this person said this and this is they're all like you can imagine how like low in the total pull. He's going like you know
It's like it's like it's so ridiculous. It's like go get a life
anyway
Mama Maria, I don't know. I don't think mama Maria is her real name, but
He'd be back she's gonna get with our bathwater. I think I know mama Maria is what I'm not gonna call her out
She's a very famous person on the show
Okay
This is KZ. Oh my gosh, it's him. He's here listening. Okay
Yeah, yes, I'm here listening
What I'm not saying anything. I would be like, I know you're here listening. Like, you know, it's not a surprise
I'm I was here today. I don't even know who Emma is first of all
You didn't go over to that discord and like are over there at everyone knows who you are now and
Scores, but my discord somebody's playing games with you. No, you're on at least at least it's this court
I got you on two
You're on Emma's Discord. I know you were in it and you said you have something you have something you have something big planned for me
Yes, you've been over in her chat. Like it's all been reported back to me. It's like you're not fooling me
Don't play it. You're playing dumb. We were talking about it on beaters the other day about how you know
Me and her we're like the first people always up on your panel
You know stopping the trouble getting people talking getting this drama starting and then you just dump us
Well, it's not my responsibility to like well first of all, yeah
I can decide who's boring or not like if you know
Anybody that has a show is like, you know trying to keep the audience entertained, right?
Okay, so second of all I and I can have anybody I want anytime I want I can I'm having you on at my pleasure right now
Because I'd like to talk to you, but do you know you know you're not even blocked in my chat anymore
I your own block. I am I know try try to be right now try to be right now. You type tonight
Yeah, and both of my accounts to your mods block me. That's what they wanted to do psyche
No, I mean the grease couldn't do that
But then another person came in I still have the discord message and he told me he was gonna do it and they did it
Okay
Well, I don't know maybe what were you saying something you were saying bad stuff in the chat like out
You're like yelling in the chat like I wasn't letting you on and stuff, but I don't have to let you on
I mean, it's like if you are boring, I mean sometimes you are boring. I mean, it's sometimes you're more interesting
I mean, but it's like I was constantly being told oh my gosh
Like, you know don't have this a person on and I kept having you on and on but it's like and then you kind of like started
I just noticed like you started getting kind of passive aggressive on like in on the
You know coming up and asking you telling you that I'm blocked in chat and you just ignored me
But I don't have time to like go as they it's a very like long process to go and unblock people from the chat
I can check it once the day
Especially after the last time I could tell you a series about the whole way you're gonna do your panel system and I respected that
Anything I said, I went and said it on beat is I don't even know who Emma is. I swear to God
I don't I don't know who Emma person is
What is it?
People are saying all kinds of things
Why people keep repeating it and it's like different people have said it and it's like and then you have something like plan for me
And you say like a sinister way and you say it like, you know, it's like what is that about?
What do you what do you like where does that thought process come from what?
So somebody told me that that you had said that you were gonna like
They're just trying to keep me off
This panel in this channel because they know I like coming over here and I enjoy this channel in this panel
Yeah, well you can be on the panel, but it's like I told you like I need the panel sponsored
I don't know if you've ever donated it like a penny, but it's like you know
I have like you know crucible ghosts
You know donating a very large amount and so and then people being mad that I give him some power on the show
It's like well
It's like if anybody that would donate donate such a large amount like you know anybody would give power on the show
Hey, I I do not knock the hustle. I don't I was I respect what you're doing
I never said anything crazy, you know, okay, well, I don't know
I'm just a passive aggressive to towards each other because I
Like to think of it because I know why I didn't because I like you
I don't want to go at you crazy like that, you know
I mean, I was fine with everybody, but it seemed like all at once, everyone started getting really weird with me and now it's not as much anymore, like I don't know if it was just me being paranoid or my mind state or something like that, but it's like I felt like...
Like everyone was like trying to like, it's like,
I don't know, just like kind of making fun of me
or like, you know, putting me down in certain ways.
And it's like, and then even you,
and it's like, and I felt like I defended you
and all this stuff.
But it's like, I can't even remember
like specific examples now.
So that's how like little it really like didn't mean to me.
Like how, you know, I just like don't like internalize
like what I consider like either like bullying or whatever.
But,
I don't know. It's like, it's just like, you know, keep it interesting and keep it going.
I can't just have people sitting on the panel though. It's like, um, uh, and so it's like,
you need to participate more and they have more conversation or like, you know, be involved more
because like a lot of times your microphone is kind of bad and it's like, you know,
but I just have you on and it's like, you know, you can hear a lot of background noise sometimes.
Yeah. Yeah. I completely understand that. You know, I always try to mute myself while I'm not
I hope I sound good and the mic is okay, but uh, yeah, I'm just in the side, but
You know, I was listening you were talking to me. I look yeah, I ain't got no ill feelings towards you
I don't hate anybody. I don't care what anybody says on online. You know, but there's no hate campaign
Okay, well
Trust me on that. I just want to be able to be able to chat again
Okay, well, you know, I'm around I'm still here and uh, who's jimmy like I don't and so
What did uh, I didn't even tell psyche what you said about him in Jimmy's chat. So what did you say about me in Jimmy's chat?
I'm beat his chest. You I know
Yeah, I'm sure you did
I know you went and I'm beat us you went on beat us after like I wouldn't let you on one night and like we're complaining on her show
And stuff like that. Yeah that night. Well, that's true
We we're all but yeah, we're all betting over there time was over there times another one who's that I'm on Jimmy's
He knows he someone's just trying to stir trouble
Yeah, but so I heard movie Jimmy's like mad at me or something or like something like he doesn't want to talk to me or something
Or he like you know, I heard like I don't think he cares
Really because he's got he's got his own issues. I think but I think he was just
Annoyed that they got you to not let him up, you know
Well, I mean
I've let him up, but it's like yeah, but it's like I don't there's like, you know, it's not worth it sometimes for three
I just don't know well enough
I've been on his show. He's like he brought me up
I've been on his show a couple times people on my show a couple times
He'd like to go have a shirt on my show and so he's never I've never like not let him up
It's just like him not him like thinking that and not coming so right
Yeah
The time
Time I know I never said you said it time. I never said you said it time. You know, I just
You were there just
I'm not denying that I was in beat is a little annoyed. I absolutely was
Well, I know but it's like and then being a it's like so what why is she so like ready to attack me on whatever like
I mean, it's like what did I do to her like what why are you attacking ways?
I'm making money or why like, you know, it's like you are knocking the hustle because it's like
I'm actually like doing they're doing well and it's like anybody should be like maybe like, you know
I'm happy for people when they find success and I say I want people to be successful and make as much money as possible
And I'm not sitting here ripping anybody off
or like being dishonest about anything, everything's up front, all the rules are in the description of the show.
And I've explained them many times, I guess some people have missed them and stuff like that sometimes, but I'm like, you know,
and I'm about like making some money on this show because...
I'm a capricorn and this is my business and so it's like
Some people some people don't need some people like just get small donations and and are happy with it
Or they even get never do it some people just do it because they like to you know talk shit in and that kind of thing
but it's like this is for me as a business and as well as like you know fun and
You know, but it's like I used to spend a lot of my time and
thought and uh you know I try and to like make a good show for everybody trying to entertain
everybody and that's like it is and the show's free you know it's like but it's like it does have
some monetized aspects that people are free to participate or not and a lot of people have decided
they would like to you and so and it's like it's fun do people get to produce the show in a way
and uh make it their own in a way and so you know it's the shows for everybody it's like uh
you know it's like uh it's
It's fun for me to do
You know again, I don't donate much I really don't donate it all to anybody too much
I enjoy coming up on your panels, but I knew I had back away
You know because you would do in the show a certain way and if I wanted to come up
I could donate I could easily donate
Well, yeah, I mean it's not it's not that it's not that everybody has to donate
It's that one person sponsors and so we've had like sponsors like today's school bath has donated five dollars
And so I'll open up the panel tonight
For everybody for like another five dollars super chat or or cash app and then at least it's like at least I can make ten dollars a
Day because you know, it's like hard if I wasn't making it anything, you know, and so I need to make sure like that
You know if I'm spending hours of my time, it's like at least get a good start and
And it's also people like to, they like to open panels like, and they can be exciting and things like that and, but I've also been free open panels this week and, you know, but I've had many sponsored it and so, and ghost has donated so much that he has several to call, you know, and so.
we have like you know a lot of open panels to go so it's like you know you don't have to pay for it but
if you want to participate in them yeah and then it's like I can be picky who I want on the show
because it is my business and so you know it's like I get to decide who I want when I want them
and uh how for how long and so I'm not gonna apologize for like
Ready my show you have your own show KZ of your channel. You can like run your channel like you want to you can do
And that's just my that's my whole point
I'm man enough to admit when I mean I had feelings in it
I was frustrated, but I understand at the end of the day like I'm over it. I'm not mad at you. I don't have this
Whole you know campaign to go after you trust me. I don't even think about it
I'm bummed I can't go into chat like I'll type in there
I was just doing it now I'll I'll I'll look I'll I'll I'll look next time I'm a next time. Oh, you know
Probably tonight. I'll look after the show. I'll go look at my like ban list and I'll see
You're there. I'll try to take you out and stuff
But I think that I saw like there's maybe only one not like more than one of your name in there
So I'll have a look of the looks okay
Appreciate that
Yeah, so what's going on anything you'd like to talk about
No, you know, I really haven't been I really don't know what's going on
I watched beat of the other day and I know you guys are going through something
But it's like you guys make up and break up every other day. All right. Yeah, I just I don't know what's going on
I'll see that she's obsessed with like biscuits or something like that. She keeps like
Talking about the biscuit song. I'm like, oh, yeah, well, I'm not really interested in the song
I mean, I think she played I think I feel like you know, I can't play music on my show
So I was like, I don't want to play it on my show and she got real mad and now she just like it's obsessed with like
Just like biscuits and that's all she'll say to me now like anymore. She just is like biscuit biscuits
That's why she was playing the biscuit song. Okay, so that was the joke. Okay, I get it
But it's not really it's like not funny. It's just like
I just don't I don't know it's like she just got mad because I would have played on my show
But it's like it's not it's like I heard it's okay
It was like I've had a funny video that I just can't play it on my show she can play on her show
I just can't play on my show. That's like the whole thing with it, but I don't understand why she keeps like
Harpy on like just this one song like I don't know if she's like I think she just likes to say the word or something like that
I don't know. She just keeps saying it over and over
And uh, that's how it's been. I don't know so I can't really respond
Anyway
Hello, yeah, yeah, I'm just okay
Yeah, I got quite so anybody else also a hey can I dry?
You are
Link, okay, hold on can a dry come on up. Yeah, can the dry was up on beat is um, you know the day when I was watching too
You're you're a can of dry your time is
Your time is you're free so come on in
But yeah, when he gets up here, I'm gonna I'm gonna
Say goodbye to you for the time being KZ because I'm going to have a closed panel for right now
Just KZ have a secret grinder account. I don't know answer that in chat
Hey, I'll see you soon
No, what's going on i'm up here to get you your bag for the day
Okay, well, I don't I don't know it's like I think that the donors have been very generous. I think that they
They're gonna keep going I went on another panel and they donated on that panel. They're they're no i'm up here, buddy
I'm getting you your bag
Oh, okay. Well, how are you tonight? I'm just chilling. I just made some teriyaki beef a little rice. I'm just hanging out
Yeah, well, it was like it's like well, I think it's pretty cool that at least the kick system is you is getting out on YouTube
because it's making some creators some money and it's like I think it's like also like a you know, I'd say I'm glad that it's
taking off as a system and
You know, it's like if you're
If part of demonstrating that you know, that's kind of cool too because it's like, you know, you're helping people make people money and
And it's like not yeah, it's nothing. It's like, you know, basically just like 24-hour thing. And so it's just a very temporary thing that
Yeah, it can be
It's every day it's every day I come up here
The same person fucking is paying to take me down. So, you know who it is
I think she made herself pretty clear last night. I'm not just trying to take credit for someone else's work, but
Yeah, it's a good time. I
Just want to drain the wallet, you know what I mean
Well, take the grandkids inheritance spend it on YouTube
Well, you know, it's like I think about money is that
You can't take it with you. You know it's like it's like
Inheritance fuck the grandkids. You know, I think there's a hopefully there's enough for both, you know
Finding out like your grandma be like so your grandmother had 25 grand for you
But she spent a lot of it fighting on YouTube panels. And so now you get this old watch
Oh, well, I don't I don't I don't I don't look at it like that. I don't I don't think that you don't have to but it's one
And it's pretty funny
Okay
So I'm just in here
I've finished my finish my one of my horror lemonade's I have a couple left. I think I have three tonight
Hopefully I'll have a
Nice sleep. Let me see Chris. Yeah. Oh, yeah, so yeah. Oh, I agree. All right. Oh, yeah, let's see
He always he's on panel time. So does site he eats tacos all like what is your people are so funny?
Hey, psych they'll just
Instead of being true to themselves,
they just make shit up to start drama.
Like you're up here eating fucking tacos all the time.
It's one of our favorite things to do.
It's to watch fucking psychic eat his fish tacos.
So I don't know what you're talking about, sweetie.
Well, I like to, I do like to, like,
I'm sorry, sweetie, I thought you were coming at me.
You're not, you're saying it's like I'm dining out.
I feel that, I feel that.
Well, I really don't mind. I really don't like I don't mind it's like, you know, but it's like it's like I know some people in chat
Chomp down on a taco buddy
Well, yeah, I mean, it's a but that's the kind of like, you know, I'm like eating for the camera
Eat for the camera. No, I know yeah, sorry. I was on edge there
Some people like to watch people eat and it's like you know well
I think more some people just hear the noises like the chewing and it's like and they don't like chewing and stuff and so
But I don't I mean I don't mind it
It's like I can barely hear right now because my ears are all clogged right now. I'm like trying to so
I'm gonna go to little
teriyaki beef here
some broccoli a
little yellow pepper there and
some rice
And
We're just cooking at home here, so
I've been I've been getting way too much
Door-dash recently and like, you know, it's like it's it's a good and something it's expensive and
Dude, yeah, when you look at how much you've spent on that shit. It just adds up so fast
I know but it is like nice to like, you know have something delivered and like not to like
This is like I try to get like, you know, I have the premium membership where it's like I get like, you know
Bigger discounts and stuff like that, but it still is pretty expensive and like
Locked my man because I don't like their negativity
Okay, yeah, he meant is I know he meant is not like chewing sounds like I know that man doesn't really
I don't know why he man just hangs around in the fucking chat
He's just a chat like all these people that never come on panel, but like live in the chat room
It says a lot about
Great he must agree mod and he must all
Even been with me when I think of a mod on YouTube. I think of like
a hairy dude with a big gut and a beard and a long ponytail sitting in a couch full of like cigarette butts and old cheese so like yeah I mean if that's a woman that's fine
but you know the typical like reddit mod joke that's how most of these people that don't come on panel that are in chat rooms
make me feel they give me the they tingle my spidey senses you know what I mean
Well, how's everyone in chat doing like he man like what do you have to say or is it what he meant say something?
I don't know. I belong to man. So I don't care what they have to say
Okay
Their responses useless
I'm gonna check out the chat.
Hold on.
Even.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh my gosh.
I never think it's the Whole Foods
or they ask me not to film or something.
No, sweet people.
It's just like, I think that it's like, you know,
it just gets a little old.
It's like going to Starbucks or the pier or like,
I wish I had like more exciting stuff to do.
And it's like, I would love to-
Let's fucking rage it up at Whole Foods, psych.
Let's go right now.
Yeah, but it's like I don't feel like getting up and like walking over there and it's the closest spot
We could go right now together. Let's go on a date. Let's go
I think I think I like I think I like I spent all my data like I'm like, you know
Just like accidentally running my phone like I just invited you on a date and you gave me the data the data drop
You're like, sorry, man. I don't have data. I can't go on. I
Can't go I can't
And my bike is like, you know, not working right now.
And so it's like, I'm not really like down like,
it's like, I'm trying to get it fixed really.
So my neighbors are there fixed it, but then I just moved.
And so she's like, oh, he'll come as soon as you can.
And it's like, I don't know.
It's like, I don't want to keep reminding them,
but it'd be awesome.
Okay, who's coming up?
Oh yeah.
So it's just they get the backstage.
So I'm going to keep it just one on one for right now.
So
I'm up here trying to get you your bag homie
Well, I don't I don't know I guess that that person is
You don't care. They're not washing. Oh, they care they care. They've been spending
Spending all your money on me and spending time on me. Oh
God
Well, so I do have you been following that
True crime case at all. The what's her name?
It's all over now, okay, there's a new case. What's the case? It's not new. It's old as fuck
cruise ship missing
What's her name?
Amy Lynn Bradley. Yeah, there's a documentary. I don't know. I thought maybe you'd seen it
I just wanted your opinion if you had seen it
I kind of I think the brother might have did it do you want the gist or no well go
ahead tell me the story what's going on so basically it's like 1998 this lesbian
girl is on a cruise with her brother and her mom and dad and she went missing on
the cruise ship
1998 so this is like this like like 30 years ago. Yeah, 27 years ago. Yeah, I know I'd say
but so
She was seen dancing with this guy
Yellow
So, I mean, is this case like
It's kind of come up again, or is it just all over Netflix? I don't know. It's getting talked about a lot right now
Basically girl goes missing after being last seen with a homie in the like cruise ships band
But then her girlfriend came and was like no, I'm pretty sure her family
Tried to give her like a lesbian intervention on the cruise ship
And they think that she like jumped overboard or through her overboard and her brother
Her brother is like a really weird creepy online Twitter account and just
Yeah, I don't know again. You haven't seen it. So it doesn't really matter
I was just curious if you had seen it
You know what your angle was
Well, it's like I don't think that somebody would like this fairly jump off of a cruise ship if they're they're family intervened
You know if they're a lesbian, I mean it just seems like that's a very extreme reaction for like coming out
Yeah, and so it was like and also like it's like not really not the right time if it's on a cruise
It seems like it's kind of so I think there was probably some kind of foul play involved or she when she disembarked or something like that
Maybe she like met met some some trouble and
Yeah, so some people believe that she like was sold to a brothel and like fucking Barbados or whatever
You know like in some fucking tropical place. Is she black? Was she black? No
I mean if it was the in the island you probably stand out
Again, I don't this isn't my story I've just been a lot of people are talking about it and I was curious if you had been
Yeah, I haven't heard about it really. Yeah, it's not it's whatever. There's there's better two crime stories out there for sure
Yeah, I mean I I've been to true crime and
It's my father was a huge crime buff
He had a whole like, you know library full of books and I love what are my favorite ones love lobster boy
Have you heard of lobster boy? No
Lobster boy his name is like Giles something he was like in this freak show because he had these lobster like hands like his hands
Were like lobster claws you can look at any styles. Okay. Yeah, great styles. Yeah, and he like basically I think he like
He he got murdered by somebody and I think if you think he was his wife or his daughter or something like that
Because he was like such a mean mean guy and
And so I just remember that I don't remember the exact story. If you look it up, you can probably guess more details about it, but it's a great and once known as lobster, the boy may have died in 1992, but his legacy of evil and hate lives on even today.
Yeah, killer carnival star fucking weird.
Yeah, you can see his hands. He has these lobster lobster if you see this picture, yeah
It's just crazy cuz like it's such a like stereotype that some weird like mangled-looking dude would be a murderer
Yeah, well, I don't know if he used the murder or he got I think he got murdered
But he might I think he was like abusive or something like that and like, you know, and so
like I think like I don't know if anyone was processing
Yeah, you can tell me can refresh my memory if you see any interesting details right there family history according to grady's father the styles family had a long history of elect a
Extradactily dating back to 1840 grady styles
Was the fourth child of Grady F. Styles. Well
He was born he was folded into his father's side show act at the age of seven
Styles was an alcoholic and abusive to his family due to his
Affliction
He wasn't able to walk while he sometimes used a wheelchair. He commonly used his hands and arms for locomotion
Interesting way to use that word he developed substantial upper body strength that when combined with his bad temper and alcoholism
Made him dangerous to others
Just swinging his claws
Yeah
He does have claws. Yeah
On September 28th, 78 in Pittsburgh,
Stiles shot and killed.
How did he shoot his oldest daughter's fiance
on the eve of their wedding?
Oh my God, you are not marrying this man.
I'm gonna kill him.
Literally Stiles did not approve of him.
He was brought to trial
where he openly confessed to killing the man.
He was not sent to prison
as no state institution was equipped
to care for an inmate with this issue.
Yeah, and it's a yeah, well, it's like if you're an a like a wheelchair
Can you imagine if you're like in a wheelchair you like murder somebody is a they're like, oh, we have to get a ramp in the prison now
We have to let you have to redo the whole thing. So they're basically they just say
Yeah, looks like is there a prison out there for people who have handicaps
I don't think so. I mean, it's like I maybe they might put them in like a like a hospital or something like that or like some kind of like
Yeah, but there are a collegiate fucking jail
You know what there are
Because I've been to I've been to County jail off the Angeles and I worked in the the kitchen as a trustee and
There are special diets and so there's all these kind of religious diets and like gluten-free diets and like sugar-free
Diabetic and like there's a million different like little special like
Mule kiss we had to prepare for like specialty prisoners and stuff like that. So
Whoa in 1992 Teresa together with her son from a previous mayor, okay wait style stop drinking after
He did this
He soon began drinking again, and his family claimed that he became more abusive.
In 92, Teresa, together with her son from a previous marriage, hired a 17-year-old sideshow
performer named Chris Wyant to kill Styles for $1,500, the equivalent of $3,300 in 2024.
The Stiles smoked a cigarette on the sofa while watching the video Monkey Boy.
Wyatt entered his home with a semi-automatic pistol and shot him in the head twice.
Yeah.
And I remember he smoked like these Paul Maul cigarettes, like he like, you know,
there's a little cheap, like discussing Paul Maul.
What a bizarre story, psyche, thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I watched a lot of, like I said, my dad would watch a lot
of True Prime, like we go on vacation, like, so I think I read that book, like there's
a book, Lobster Boy, it's a really good book, actually, the whole book and the whole story.
Yeah, it was a great book.
Yeah, I'm trying to think about like then otherwise, you know, there's just the big famous cases and like, you know
But I'm always like going down the rabbit hole with like taking a lot of these are like conspiracy theories or like or like
You know Psyops like you know fake stories like I kind of don't believe in John Wayne Casey or like
Ted Bundy I think that there's like code names and the names and if you look at the victims names
There's code codes and those if you know what to look for you know
But it's like if you think they were like scapegoats for what was really going on
I think it's like programming the culture because it's like I don't really think that the serial killing is that common like where there would be like a kid like you know, like I'm Jack the Ripper or something like that, or like, you know,
yeah, I think like a lot of it is just programming the culture to like either be afraid and like to be on edge that there's like serial killers or like, or just to put
You know these they because it's like all these emotional cases they raise the emotions of the person then it's easy to like
Have a program the person when they're in a state of emotion, you know
It's easier to program the subconscious and stuff like that
If they Albert fish was fake
Yeah, because look at and look at the name it's like our fish. It's like and then
You know he was the a lot of the state people that make stuff out of skin and stuff like that
Our fake even like the the Auschwitz that Bishop Burke involved or wherever she was she I'm gonna look into this
That's an interesting
idea, but like
So if you look at the human skin lampshades that there's supposedly like something in the HOL
C-A-U-S-C, you know, like they're like there's supposedly there's these were things that were made
But it was like this was kind of like exaggerated and like there was a lot of
Stuff that was made up just for shock value during the time and there was of course after the
H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T there was of course like a lot of people that were just railroaded and like you know
Because there was a big call for justice or whatever after
Have you ever heard of?
David and Robert Picton
No, who are they?
Very real serial killers from from Canada
They were from where my girlfriend's from, the same town, in Abbotsford, so just outside
of Vancouver and they had a pig farm.
And they were very involved with bikers, weird occult motherfuckers and all this shit.
they pay and bring all these prostitutes out to their pig farm and they'd grind
up their pigs and make pies like the whole thing and these guys I forget how
many prostitutes they they killed and made into pork sausage and sold out in
Vancouver and it's very real like it really happened it was like one of the
craziest things
And every once in a while, you'll meet someone in Vancouver who knew them or, you know, lived down the street and it's just fucking crazy, bro, the shit that went on on the picked and farmed.
Yeah, well, I've actually, I've done some like family research and like I've traced some of my ancestry to like some guy in a
I think Iceland or Greenland and his name is Axler Bjorn or something like that
And he actually was an axe murderer and I've heard my ancestry to him
like through DNA and
He was the first of murder and in a green that home. What was it?
I think it was the in a great of Iceland, which is which is like the greener one, right?
And he was the only serial killer there and he like found this axe
I would know like speak to him and like the axe told him to kill people and I guess he killed a lot of people
He was a serial killer and I think the only one there. I don't know just random
I see what you're saying though. Like you think it's more rare than the media had portrayed it
Yeah, I mean it's like
Yeah, at least the serial killers, like, you know, John Wayne Gasey had like 33 bodies under his floorboards, right?
And then they have like people taking them out. It wasn't like a bunch of like police.
It was all these guys in sports jerseys and stuff like that and with like numbers prominently displayed on them
and I believe in like, you know, they use numerology to like show certain things, you know,
Yeah, do you look at a lot of and also like a lot of news stories they'll have like
Certain colors like Tiffany blue. Also, they'll be wearing like certain hats of sports teams or like certain fraternity
There's just like little signs
If you know what to look for you'll see them everywhere
And so it's like I can't really watch the news anymore because it's just it all seems fake to me
I know what you stumbled upon that helped you decode this idea
Was it a video or like where?
I just, I would say just studying the occult and like, like, gematria and like, getting into numerology, gematria and then symbolism.
Right, but is there like a specific guy I could watch?
Hmm. Well, there's like a lot of stuff on YouTube that is like, you know, like
It's the guy called decode yourself. I think is one guy and it's like, you know, there's a guy could does a guy named doughnut
DOE and UT and like he's I think he's a Jewish guy
But it's the Freemason and like there's a lot of freemasons. There's a guy named paranoid American
Like you can watch paranoid American and they won't necessarily tell you everything like this like because like I'm telling you but they will
But they'll present it like it's actually like real real stuff like you know the present, you know
They'll present it and like it's you know, but I I think it's like, you know
Psi up and everything that's they're kind of like we've had tongue-in-cheek like they'll kind of like point out some of it
They kind of mixed truth with lies, too
But those are so I used to watch those but I don't know how like it's just like setting the occult and like even
setting old Freemasonry books or you know Albert Pike and you can read like he if you read like
Albert Pike's big book, Morals and Dogma, it has basically an encyclopedia of all this
different symbolism, and then you'll notice a symbolism all throughout the media and things
today.
It's because it's all run by basically.
A lot of it's run by this organization, right, or this brotherhood and so, but it's so events you learn about that and you learn about the biblical
Influences, and then you start seeing the biblical names and stuff like that and some of the victims lists and things are in the different like names like King and
You just like learn that it's like the world is kind of a stage like Shakespeare, right?
It's like the world's the stage world players on the stage. He just plays our part kind of thing
Hi guys
Hey, oh, yeah guys, by the way, I didn't get like a I got a message from
Murna, I want to share this is like, you know, Michael like with like with Simons
You know, I hope she's okay with me sharing this
But yeah, this is from Murna who was on the show and we remember remember we always had
You know the controversy like the people and stuff like that, you know, it was Michael a little bit
But she didn't send me a message. It's really nice. She said
She said psyche by now, you know probably no Michael pass Michael L passed away on July 18th
Hold on
You see
Oh, something went wrong. Okay, hold on. I'm trying to get this message you all okay
Okay, on July 18th, I just wanted you to know how greatly he appreciated your online friendship.
You have a great influence on people through your online channel and Michael felt loyal
to you through this past year.
He would always say, I want to go on panel and support Psyche.
He was often misunderstood for who he chose to portray himself as and said things he shouldn't
But in reality, he surely was a sensitive, loyal loving, loyal guy, opinionated, and
curious about things he often questioned.
I choose to honor his memory with the good times.
I hope you and the rest of the community does as well.
I have always believed that love conquers evil, much peace and love to all.
Myrna.
She like put his quote, which he would always say he always said every day above ground is a good day
Sorry
Yeah, that was nice. I'm gonna jump down and let random guy up, okay
Thank you. I'll be back. Okay. Thank you, Canada. I'll be back
Okay. See you later
I'll be right back random guys. Sorry. I wasn't looking at the screen. I'm sorry. I
Apologize
Bye. I'll see you later
Yeah, catch you later dude catch you later. See ya, bro
Later, I'll be back later on. Okay
Okay
I don't think so time. Come on, but I do hope Mara comes and like, you know, I'm shares of message and stuff like that
Yeah, the funeral was yesterday. You saw you thought you saw that in the Bishu area. Oh
Yeah, here's the link. I'm sorry. Here you go
Yeah, it's kind of it's kind of sad, you know, I mean it is very sad, you know, it's pretty sudden
It's like not process, you know, it's like sometimes we just think and like
You know, I missed the guy
Hi, I made a song you did I don't have time for no gay shit here goes
I
Don't know if that's like a copyright song or whatever, but I don't want to play that song. Okay. I'd like you random guy
I just don't want to play this. I have a song to play here
Wrenched like a sword in the stream
Emma Leviathan, Demon Queen Divine
Read the cards, stole my soul and crossed the line
She was Satan's ex, with that fiery stare
Told me my rising sign, like she actually-
I'm stuck in there.
Hi guys. Oh, I'm being good. Yeah, this is Dracula.
Sokibus, yep.
Um, no, random guy can't play the song, but all it can is drive back.
Oh, hello.
up the way. This one's to sit back stage. Yeah. I got drinks tonight. Yeah. So I finished
this one. I have a couple more. Oh, Spunky did today. Guys, if you, if I'm on and like
Spunky's on, just let me know, like, which she's on. And I'll like, I'll just like send
And I'll go over there too. I feel bad
That I didn't the other night
But I had just gone on like 1130 and I was like I didn't know how long she's gonna be on so I don't know cooking dinner. Yeah
Hmm so
Cheers guys, this is the smirnoff pineapple coconut. I don't know if I'm gonna get anything else tonight. Oh
I'm sorry. I missed it. Sweet pea
You told me a Samans. I'm sorry. You're stoned. Oh, excuse me. I'm very stoned, too
Looking for my where's my
Well, I have a oh here it is on my lap
Canada dry when you want to come back up you have to go show me yourself on screen
I'm confused what's going on
I tend to bring you back up, but then
I brought you up before you weren't there
So I was like I want to send you to see you on screen
So I know you're there. So we're gonna bring you up
You know
I think I think I get it
Yeah, because I try to bring you up before and you weren't there
So I just want to make sure you were there. Oh, I was muted there. Yeah, okay
Yeah, so like I clean my I've been cleaning my apartment today, and I did all my laundry
I like clean my table off. It's like so clean in here. It's like so different. It's like that's nice
Can you see yourself? Yeah, you make it sing your song. Have you even come up?
Yeah, but uh
I'm slowly getting it all cleaned up and it's gonna look really good and
Then I'll get my new computer and that'll be really cool. I have a really nice microphone I can use
That's like a professional microphone.
And so my show should sound a lot better.
Let me see.
You can record your new demo.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I'm getting better
at the AI stuff too, the AI music and stuff.
And I'm also working with the chat GPT
like really closely on my show.
Like it's like, I'm telling you a lot about my show
and it gives me a lot of good advice.
Maybe you should start pre-recording bedtime story segments and having them uploaded
People might like to listen to you read them a story at bedtime
Well, I do I mean, I do like read and it's like people do like to like listen to me read and stuff like that
I just need to like, you know do it the right time
You know, yeah, yeah, you know like psyche reads, you know, Fox and the hound
Yeah, I've heard I've read a lot of ace-hop spables and
Fairy tales I like I like reading those kind of things. I I mean I like those but I like those in general like I can
I'm gonna look up ace-hop spables right now and read a few of those because they're I
Don't know if you read Fox in the Hound
Well, I read it. No, that's like a Disney a Disney book, you know, it's like but there probably is like a fox and a dog
Um asos fable maybe that may be the fox in the house based on that
Let me see. Let me see if they have something close to that. They do have a
Dogs and the fox. Okay, so it's there you know
It said some dogs found the skin of a lion and furiously to get to tear it with their teeth
A fox chance to see them and laugh scornfully
If that lion had been alive, he said it would have been a very different story
He would have made you feel how much sharper his claws are than your teeth
is that it is easy and also contemptible to kick a man that is down, that is the moral of that.
Then this one's called the dog and the hides. I said some hungry dogs saw a number of hides
at the bottom of the stream where the tanner had put them to soak. A fine hide makes an excellent
meal for a hungry dog but the water was deep and the dog did not reach the hides from the bank.
So they held a council and decided the best thing to do was to drink up the river.
all fell to lapping up the water as fast as they could.
But though they drank and drank until one after another,
all of them had burst with drinking,
still for all their effort,
the water in the river remained as high as ever.
And it says, do not try to do impossible things.
That's a pretty interesting one.
Ah, let me see what else.
You like that?
This one's called the rabbit, the weasel, and the cat.
A rabbit left his home one day for a dinner of clover,
but he forgot to latch the door of his house,
and while he was gone, a weasel walked in
and calmly made himself at home.
When the rabbit returned, there was the weasel's nose
sticking out of the rabbit's own doorway,
sniffing the fine air.
The rabbit was quite angry for a rabbit
and requested the weasel to move out,
but the weasel was perfectly content.
He had settled down for good.
A wise old cat heard the dispute and offered to settle it.
Come close to me, said the cat.
I am very deaf.
Put your mouth close to my ears while you tell me the facts.
The unsuspecting pair did as they were told,
and in an instant the cat had them both under her claws.
No one could deny that the dispute had been definitely
settled.
It's as if the strong are apt to settle questions
to their own advantage.
Okay, then we got the bear and the bees.
A bear roaming the woods in search of berries
happened upon a fallen tree
in which a swarm of bees has stored their honey.
The bear began to nose around the log very carefully to find out if the bees were at
home.
Just then one of the swarm came home from the clover field with a load of sweets.
Guessing what the bear was after, the bees flew at him, stung him sharply and then disappeared
into the hollow log.
The bear lost his temper in an instant and sprang upon the log tooth and claw to destroy
the nest.
But this only brought out the whole swarm.
and he was able to save himself only by diving into a pool of water.
And it says it is wiser to bear a single injury in silence than to provoke a thousand by flying into a rage.
Wow, that's a good one.
What do you think?
Is there a shadow band? Why does it happen? It happens if you um if you have too much like
Don't know guys if you search search psyche awakens tarot and see if I come up and if I don't then I'm probably shadow band
You know and it's like it just comes up because there's either like the wrong thing said on the show
I don't know sometimes
sometimes
non monetized channels get shadow bands to you like more often
I don't think mine shadow band though
Hey, here's one called the dog in the manger
A dog asleep in a manger filled with hay was awakened by the cattle, which came in tired
and hungry from working in the field, but the dog would not let them get near the manger
and snarl and snap as if they were filled with the best of meat and bones, all for himself.
The cattle looked at the dog and discussed how selfish he is, said one, he cannot eat
the hay and yet he will not let us eat it, who are so hungry for it.
Now the farmer came in, when he saw how the dog was acting, he seized the stick and drove
with many a blow for selfish behavior. It says, do not grudge others which you cannot enjoy yourself.
Okay, I have one more. The wolf and the goat. A hungry wolf, spied a goat.
browsing at the top of a steep cliff where you could not possibly get to her.
This is a very dangerous place for you, he called out pretending to be very anxious about the goat's safety.
What if you should fall? Please listen to me and come down.
How can you get all you want of the finest, here you can get all you want of the finest, tenderest grass in the count country.
The goat looked over the edge of the cliff.
How very, very anxious you are about me, she said, and how generous you are with your grass.
But I know you, it's your own appetite you are thinking of, not mine.
There's an invitation prompted by selfishness is not to be accepted.
Is there any n words? I don't think so. It was written by Aesop and this was in ancient Greece.
The lights are pretty cool. Thank you. Yeah, these are world borealis. It's like a little cool
light I got. I also have this really cool spunky got me this really cool neon with the
alien with the cat. My little alien friend. You guys love that?
Pretty cool. Oh, I'm getting a text message. Let me see. Oh
Just people on tiktok
But I'm enjoying tiktok, too. I'm already monetized on tiktok
I don't know if you guys are on tiktok, but it's actually a cool site
It's a little bit different than that
YouTube but you can you know friend people there and so it's kind of easier to direct message sometimes it's hard to direct message on
on YouTube right
Did anybody check out Daddy Bigness?
He was gone today.
Oh, guys, by the way,
it is Minnie Manson's birthday today, I think.
Minnie Manson's birthday.
Yes!
Happy birthday, Minnie Manson.
Yeah, we had fun with Minnie Manson.
Fuck yeah!
Did you like the Minnie Manson interview?
Did you see it, that one?
I interviewed-
I thought Minnie Manson was kind of fucked up,
but yeah, no, I was there.
It was a good time.
Yeah, well the mini man has come on several times like yeah, he's been on like four or five times
He hasn't been on in a while though
I so if you guys can like you know say hey go back to psyche's sometime
He wants to chill with you let him know that uh, I'm still down there. Yeah, oh
Excuse me, but we had a fun time. I had a fun time with mini man, so
Many man sins are cool
Interesting performer
We'll do it. We just have a look at
See I
Thought many Manson didn't like being called to do
No, it isn't like being around other way around other way around. Oh
because he is a woman but he's
posing I think
No, I think born biologically was born a female and then now lives as a man.
If he related to Marilyn Manson, no, he's just inspired by him.
You know?
Yeah, he's inspired by him.
I think he was in love with Marilyn Manson for a period of time
and would make out with his photo and stuff like that.
He told me that story a few times.
Now he doesn't like him very much. I've heard he's also on America's Got Talent
I think this season like he went and auditioned and show me some of the video
I did a little interview about so talent
Well, I mean, I think he is like I love his more at the more at more at Billy. I don't know if you know
Yeah, it's
timeless
I think I don't you were last time. It was funny. I was I drink. Oh, you'll call. Yeah. Thank you Nancy
Yeah, thank you. I'd love to talk to many Manson and wish many Manson a happy birthday
I think I didn't like like his post but uh
Yeah, Nancy crazy to interview. He has parents somewhere somewhere many Manson's parents
shot him out however many years ago today and
Little did they know what they were, you know conjuring up in the process
well
Oh, he's pretty interesting guys. Thank you Nancy
When you have sex in a back alley kids
Well, actually like a mini man said actually was on please believe it or not as a female and because he had
He had a cat even or not
Yeah, and his cat was like heads like a little like
The tail had like a little me like a little question mark
You're like all white the cat was black the tail was like me a question mark
And then there's like a little dot a perfect dot at the like right place for the explanation for the
Hey, Daddy, how are you?
so
No, yeah, so Mary so so you're saying Ripley's believe it or not was having a pretty rough year with
With unbelievable
Well, no, I mean it's like it doesn't one of the episodes that he was on and I saw that and it's like it'll biopic
anywhere
I got cigarettes today. I know they're terrible, you know, adult smoke people, but yeah
I got some cigarettes today because they don't sell my they don't sell the cigars
Well, they do sell cigars, but they're backwoods and so it's like
literally or like they were
Rolled into a tobacco leaf in the back woods of like Arkansas or something like that
Just like by like two guys and like a back of a truck or something and it's like thrown into like, you know
Packaging because they say they're just falling apart and it's like they're just terrible
I think you're just supposed to use them for like
Like a weed wrap or something and throw away the tobacco, but anyway, so
Uh, they're expensive if I put the cigarette out you'll donate $20. Okay
But I might
I'll put it out, but what if I wanted to smoke another one? I won't okay. Well, if you do that if you donate $20
I will not smoke another one tonight. You don't like cigarettes. Okay
I'm gonna choose you back though, but it's like I just there's like they don't sell the
Swisher sweets here anymore because it has the word sweet in it
And they don't sell black and miles because it has the word miles on it
And so it's like if you think it's going to influence people to smoke or something
and so but I put the cigarette out and
Hey, oh look at this Fred I had Fred else. There's a guy up here. Goddy. Come on up buddy
Yeah
Maybe seems like a dragon. Well, look at you. Uh, it's because you had a copyright sweep you had a copyright. Oh my god
It was you Johnny come on here, but
Okay, yeah, well random random guy was you know
Very random guy can come up and I thought he left
Okay, got it. I'm pretty I'm lighting the cigarette back up like the cigarette is being relit
No, he's gonna please know he said he don't need to ammo a bite and then that does not count
Okay
So I'm relighting it. He donated $20 in your name to make a wish
Oh
So good
Oh, I love the taste of a cigarette. She's a thank you over. Yeah, well, whatever Joe Gotti get up here, buddy
Don't make me play the song again
I'm gonna smoke the cigarette. Yes, I'm going to keep it in spite of God II spite of God
And spying on my rage, I am still just having a dream.
Hey, look who's here.
Mini-Mantin, I have to remodge you.
I feel the reason it's like you're not
is because I had unmodded everybody,
but I have to remodge you, I'm sorry.
Do you remember when Billy Corgan told Howard Stern
that he had seen someone's shape shift?
Well, tell me about it.
Billy Corgams on the Howard Stern show and you told him this story about how he saw this woman
Changed her face
Hi man
Happy birthday and everyone say happy birthday to Minnie Manson
Here you go. Happy birthday. Happy birthday Minnie
Yeah, there you go, thank you for coming awesome
Yeah, I'm not I'm I remodeled you here. You're you're modded. You're fine
Many man's actually a managing mod, so you know you guys really got to behave yourself, but
Hi, happy birthday many man's and hey, let's all sing happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, Mini Manson, happy birthday to you, and many more.
Happy birthday, yeah, as long as it's your birthday.
I heard it's your birthday, dinner, dinner, yeah.
If you want to come up on the panel, I will kick off Canada Drive.
Let me know if you, I'm just kidding, I will.
But if you do want to come on the panel, here's the link.
I've just been doing one at a time, people, anyway lately, but, of course.
So then he went on Joe Rogan and he told the same story, anyways, some people on the internet
have figured out that it was Tila Tequila.
Oh, there's a really okay, mini-man. I love you. Have a good night. Have a fun night. Okay. Love you
Teela tequila actually teela tequila. There's a great video on YouTube you have to search for and it's teela tequila
Daptizing the neighborhood kids now. I'll be right back. I'll be right back
Where we going? Good. Hi. Oh, I'm just doing one at a time right now because I actually
What's his school? The Athens donated five dollars today
So tonight if you want to open the panel or anybody wants to open the panel
It's just five dollars and I'll open the panel because he donated earlier. So he donated half. Okay. Yeah
You know what we have to do you have to run a tab for me. I
Have I have a book I've written everything down on my little book
You know, so yeah, we could run a tab and then at the end of the year
I could just send you a check. Oh you want to do a tab you want to run credit on my show Goddy like a bar
Okay, like a bar. Okay. Yeah, I'm good for it. Okay, would you like me to put the $5 in your tap tonight and open the panel?
Not right now. No, okay. Well, can I try sorry I tried I tried for you
He's the one who told me to come up here.
I know.
I put him right backstage because I said one at a time and we're going to stick to it.
I didn't have the panel open like yesterday, the day before yesterday.
No, it's just five dollars for anybody.
It's five dollars, one person, sponsors, and then everybody can join the panel.
But right now I'm just going to do one-on-one and that's, you know.
My I was gonna respect you and you wanted to be with a mini but a mini said screw you. Yeah
It's okay
Well, I hope many many you can do whatever they he wants to do tonight because it is his night
He's his birthday today. So happy birthday. We just want to make sure and he has a good night
And just what he wants and so
Yeah, and so if someone would like to donate a $5 super chat, then I will open the panel
We do have Canada Drive SIG backstage who I will bring up if somebody gets SIG up. Yeah, he wants to wish many a happy birthday, too
Okay, well someone would like to drop five dollars super chat or cash up. It's on the screen
Five pesos. No, nope. No, no has to be American D narrow
500 pennies
It's I think it's a pretty pretty
reasonable
Um, actual price, but yeah, if you'd like to have SIG and the Canada drive up here with God
You know, I can probably make it happen
But if not, I'm just gonna be talking to God and I'm happy as the taking shit doing that, right?
Like listen before you say that I don't want to aggravate you anything. I want to ask you a serious question
Sure, don't get offended. Please don't get offended. I got my there's a reason why I'm asking you this
He's gonna get that face like you ready to get a
Don't get offended. Don't get offended, right? When was the last time?
Don't don't don't do that to your eyes because I know you're getting ready to get fucking mad. You're ready to kick me off the panel
What was the last time you got paid for a tarot reading?
I got paid for a tear reading. I would say well, I've been doing them on on
TikTok
And so I get
Okay, yeah, I've been doing it there and actually it's a better format
You know how I do like really quick readings like I took that on YouTube on YouTube people like like long drawn out things
You know sometimes I just thought it would be like when I when I watched hair channels on YouTube
I get kind of bored watching other people's readings
I'm more interested in my own and sometimes it takes forever to get to me and stuff like that for people that do long readings
Right, and so I've just been used to doing
fast readings on YouTube, but it's actually a perfect format for a for TikTok is the fast readings and people love it
And then I just have a little banner
It says it says type your question in chat and people will you know
Thank me and maybe like I've also almost booked some readings there too, but I've booked readings
I can I book readings I get tip for readings
I I get but it's like you know since beat has been slandering me about like oh, you know
He needs cards to read and like blah blah blah. It's like that. I know it's like
The only reason I asked you that I'm not trying to be an asshole is because the channel seemed to be getting away from that with the paid
Panels and stuff like that where you make your more money with that then you
Were getting away, but I forgot you went to TikTok and you're doing that there, which is great
Yeah, and I really I mean that's the perfect place for that and so it also my quick readings work work perfect there
And and on the YouTube, you know, it's like you do a work hand-trackable you do it works
And so if it's like, you know, but you know, you can see like nobody's really donating right now
$5 remember I asked you for a car
I said I don't want more than one car because I don't want to take up your time with the reading
Especially that you know, it's plus you were doing it for free, which I appreciated
Yeah, you don't want to do the long thing because you know, it's up to time that other people can get a reading with
Right and also like, you know, I would I would I would do longer like people say oh his readings are stored whatever
Yeah, I do quick readings because I've been doing them for free if I if I have a paid reading
I will take more time with it and pull more cards of course
But it's like it seems like a lot of people here are not like from the tarot community either a lot of people here are from
The panel verse and enjoy the panels and the drama and that kind of stuff
And I like I'm gonna keep it tarot themed as much as I can
I did like take all the cards off my table. They're on my other table right now
So I have to get up and like find a deck. I want to use tonight and everything if I do
Bring them down tonight, but uh, I don't know. I just I was
Keep it like, you know, whatever works, you know, it's like this is my first month
I made over a thousand dollars on YouTube. I'm Goddy great man. That's great. Thanks. Thanks to those guys who paid
You know the ghost and uh random and whoever that's awesome
Yeah, and that's and for anybody that doesn't think it's possible to make money on YouTube
It is very possible, you know, but I have done it every I'm on it every day
I'm like here every day and like trying different things and some things work something so you know
I get a lot of shit for anything. I try to you know, and so I
But I thank you guys for being on the journey with me. It's okay a raiser. Don't worry about it
It's not like I'm trying to like, you know
you know strong arm anybody for anything it's like I understand people are of
different economic backgrounds and abilities and things like that if you're
here participating in chat you're doing plenty it's like that's all I ask is
like even if you're not participating in chat if you give a like at least and or
at least a friend of the show and like you know stick up for me sometimes if
you see
i'm being attacked someplace i appreciate that i appreciate it i do like get to see like a lot of
stuff talked about me i do watch a lot of stuff with the problem with you is and it's not a problem
i'm just using problem as the term is that you got all this other shit other than being pure tarot
you know you got all these people coming at you you you do other topics you talk about other
things you want you know your friends to stop by you talk with them you know if you were pure tarot
You'd be doing readings all day and you know, there'd be a different story
Yeah, and I say I am and right now. I'm also focused on like I'm creating this tarot deck
I want to make a psyche awakens tarot deck
What thing is that deck and I'm like working with that deck on my show and then it's like I'll be I think people will
Want to get this deck too because there's a lot of you can be love the panel of first people
Hey, Marcy you're on your way to LA staying at your sister's and driving to San Diego. Oh awesome
I'll hope we have a great trip Marcy have safe travels and everything
Marcy it's dangerous out there. Yeah, watch out for the you know LA LA can be kind of crazy driving so
Yeah, so I have a great trip Marcy. Yeah, have fun. Can you get a book update?
I'm also gonna be doing the book too. You know, I have like a lot of the I have the trolling the art of trolling
I have the whole like, you know, I know I've learned the whole psychology of trolls every oh, but they're after it
Oh, yeah a lot of good
Well, they're after some kind of fuel and it's kind of like a narcissist
The doctor's fuel and so what it's a fuel is something that just feeds them and that's going to be either
They're gonna get it from your reaction. And so that's basically what they're just going after
They're trying to get a reaction. They're trying to get somebody out of their element. They're confused
I've said angry flustered
Trying to defend themselves and all this kind of stuff
They're just trying to get a reaction if you just ignore them
They basically would just get bored like go on to the next it's like find it like a be like to go to the flower
There's no pollen left and never gonna go to the next flower, right?
Oh, they pull up their balls on panel and they fucking just give you a final. Oh, yeah
I'll do that. Yeah, I'll do that. I mean, I was there. Unfortunately. I was fucking there
Yeah, I mean it's like in that I and also I had the really nice guy the other day
You know daddy bigness or Andrew and then I did a great interview and then like somebody pulled out there
Oh, they put on poor mom at that time. But yeah, it's just like, you know, horrible horrible
I'm getting kind of hungry now. I think I think I might have to get food tonight, too
I ate today, but I'm like probably gonna have some more coffee and like food
I just said I'm like hungry. I'm so hungry tonight. Yeah, get something good, man. Don't get that shit. You always eat
Well, this is one place they get it's like 75% off on door dash and it's like I've been getting these like huge
Huge meals for like under $20 like and they're like, you know a huge
S'mores s'mores milkshake with like smirnoff and like oh here it is home
Oh, it's only 50% off tonight. Nancy. You're gonna be gaining weight with that about time
You know what? Put me backstage for a minute and put our seat up here. Maybe you can suggest something good for you to eat.
Okay. No, no, nobody's here. Nobody's backstage, but thank you.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. Well, I was like, yeah, oh, it did. Now they're 50% off instead of 75% off.
And so fuck that. You know what I'm saying? I have to find a better deal. Let me see.
I would have to for go if the meal cost $100 you're getting for 25 bucks
You know you had to pay for I was buying it
I was getting like $15 and it was 75% off
So I was getting for like $15 plus like you know I had to tip and stuff like that, but if that's it was pretty amazing
Yeah, yeah, it was a really good deal
Look at this barbecue place and Bob's barbecue. It says it's see items and I can get oh I can get buy one
Go in free street corn
beef hot link and baked beans.
And so that'd be five, nine, 10, 11, 12, W13 dollars.
Hold on, maximum three of the same items.
So two, four, six, okay.
Okay, so now I have my $15.
With that, what else do I want?
Is there anything to drink?
Is there like a coffee?
If there's not a coffee, I'm not into it.
Let me see, there's not a coffee.
There's not, oh, we'll fuck that.
Um
Wienerschnitzel $5.25 barbecue near me 20% off up to $11
Well, if you're making fun of me in the chat, what's going on?
Okay, so funny
Okay
that's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not what it's not
Yeah, it says they are crispy wings tossed in a vibrant Carolina gold mustard sauce the sauce is a tangy and slightly sweet blend of yellow mustard
Vinegar honey and spices delivering unique and bold flavor profile that combines the sharpness of mustard with a touch of sweetens
I got some blue cheese on there. Okay
Okay, and what else do I want? Let me see do they have a burger get like a big burger like a pound burger one pound
I think any place with a coffee, okay?
So that's a no no get a coffee
A coffee what coffee milkshake
Coffee milkshake that sounds good. Well, they have this okay. It's chicken shack. They have but let me see what else
They've been being the me's coffee place. I love being these copies really good. Have you ever had that? I don't drink coffee, but it sounds strong
Yeah, it's really good. It's a Vietnamese coffee. Let me see. Oh crispy cream
$3.00 off 15, but you know how expensive crispy cream is it's like so expensive. Oh
Joe's here. He wants to join him and his sister want to come up
Okay, Joe
I'll get off the panel for you both. Let them both up though. Don't just let one at a time
Of course
They're like a couple
Couple of fucking assholes
Oh Godie
Okay, what don't appear here. I'll put the link up for you guys
Hurry up. So yeah, they thought McDonald's doesn't have coffee. Yeah, but I'm at McDonald's is not very good, you know
If I got oh my gosh
If I was missing at the coffee, it'd be $17. They would be a $10 be on it. Wow
That but that's any but once I put them the
for original
Really a four glaze. Oh my gosh
Three of them are $11. That's so much. That's too much money for
For doughnuts free doughnuts $12.00. That's crazy. I'll love you God. I'm married Joe. I'll say okay
Love you. Let's take him in
I'm gonna have to leave and come back
Well, now everyone's left me there was a joke not that's a joke you left me you left me alone
Everyone now everyone left at once what's going on
You see
Semin rules they have coffee here. I'll eat a couple similar rules
They don't even have here we go
What's up big dog, what's outside you know
Happy happy Saturday, buddy, it's not Saturday at Thursday Joe
Do I got to leave and come back? I can't hear you. Are you muted?
It's Thursday. Do you hear me?
Hey, I heard my volume down. Sorry, Suggie.
this Thursday Joe
You just roll your eyes like oh Joe's here again. I hate him, but the chat likes him
So I got to let him on stop rolling your eyes psyche. I see the hate in your glasses
I don't have any I don't have hate in my heart. I don't have hate in my heart
You're playing a fucking Tetris while I'm trying to fucking have a conversation buddy
Just let me talk to my friend Ken, please come on
How you been big girl, I'm not bad. How are you doing tonight?
I feel bad because I feel like if I ever donate to you,
could you do me a favor,
not tell anybody that I donated to you?
Because if I donate to you and then somebody hears it,
like good times, he'll be like,
well, why is he donating to him and not me?
So I'd like one thing I do like about Sandman,
he keeps his donators anonymous.
Because if I, like I said, if I donate,
say right now I donate like 20 bucks.
Every beat it's gonna be like well, I'll let them on my panel. Where's my 20 bucks?
So it's like you if you get it if you get a little hundred dollar tick
Just don't even tell anybody about it. I won't I was a joke. I'm giving them hundred dollars. Yeah, you're giving me
Yeah, I don't think you're doing it one one penny
Have you done it a penny? Well, I donated my brain. What about? Oh, you're saying my brain's not even worth a penny
Oh my god, like you just said my brain's not worth a penny basically. I think you've never donated a penny yet
Well
Kim, do you know psyche were a thong will fortune July and I screenshot of it and I lick my phone screen every time
I look at that picture. You know that did you know that?
You didn't want to know that well guess what this is like his panel and it's too much information. It's like a
You know blogger's trying to look like you he's trying to grow his hair like you like blogger thinks he's you man
Yes, what do you think about people trying to look like you? He's just so handsome. I mean, it's like, you know, it's it's very plattering
Go it's like
Very flattering. I'm literally talking my phone to my ear. Holds. I can barely hear you big dog turn your microphone off
Please
Now you're better. I knew you're better
Okay
Joe, I think you're Marcia. I said Joe Joe Joe Marcia hundred dollars. I
Don't Marcy. No, I don't know Marcy hundred dollars. I don't even know Marcy. I only know her from like
Did she say I owe a hundred dollars? Yeah
Well, then you know what you need to do you need to start banning the liars people in your chat that tell lies like Marcy
You should start banning them like Marcy. I've never even met you and never even talked to you
What do you stand it in my closet for Kim? Why are you standing in my closet?
You know what I use that charger for I shove the prongs on my ass and shove the
What do you want? I use it for my good day of the vacuum dumbass
So it's like you my vacuum actually show my vacuum I
Don't know what size it is. What size is this show my vacuum, please?
Sorry, Saigi. I know it ain't all about me, but I'm just so excited.
Me and Aldi watched the whole Lions and Chargers came and the Lions got their ass kicked.
And good times didn't even show up. It was so sad.
Like, oh, my team can't even win.
But at least I got a garden.
Like, what guy even has a...
Show him my vacuum.
Hold it. Hold the vacuum.
Sorry, psych. Sorry. Sorry about that. Why do you got a cuss like yeah, though? Like say hi to him
We said you look better than ever sweetie, but he said why do you got a ball patch on the side? He never said that
And I asked you a question Kim this like he looked like Jeffrey Dahmer a little bit in 2025
I like it actually. I actually like
No, this is how dedicated he is to Halloween he's doing this Halloween costume in August
He's not a creepy guy
He's gave me so many
Like me. Oh, thank you. Thank you. I'll say you're great. I just said you look creepy
Okay, well
Sorry about that. You've hurt my feelings now
Thank you for having me on so I guess it's been a pleasure. I'm not leaving welcome. Okay
I'm just looking for, I'm looking for something to eat. Let me see. I'm looking at some calzones now. Let me see.
They wanted to get a tattoo the other day and I was like, look, I don't need hepatitis B.
Are you fucking stupid?
I don't need hepatitis C.
That's just like me telling you.
It's a joke.
It's a tattoo joke.
That you literally have bugs in every house that you exterminated.
Don't go get them.
Get out of my house.
Get out.
Get out of my house if you want to say that.
If you're going to say that in front of my friends.
You don't talk in front of my friends like that.
That's serious.
You don't tell my friends.
You don't talk in front of my business like that.
Like, literally, that's my work.
That's how I make money.
I get that joke, but some jokes aren't funny.
That's why people take shit so fucking serious and why didn't like laugh when I said it
Why did psyche live when I said it?
That's just like you telling in the psychics are fucking not true. No, you don't believe in terror cars
I do believe a terror car
It's like you saying that you that you don't believe there. No, it's pronounced like say the word care
And I'm gonna see you try to write errant. I got my own tear
Oh, you got Tarot cards. Oh, Tarot cards.
Psyche, I wish your whole deck of cards would fit on my asshole.
You understand that? See, that's basically like a porn bomb without doing it.
That's a verbal porn bomb. Like, picture that happening right now.
Picture that whole deck. Why? Why?
That's in memory of Aldi. That's what Aldi would say, and Aldi's not in that up here.
Oh, did you watch the live stream of all these funeral or not all these funeral Aussie funeral and Sharon was crying, bro
That was sad. It was fucked up. Oh my god. She was fucking done. Did they show up for Aussie though?
So I'm gonna show up for Aussie and I'm gonna say this now
Because I truly do believe this and I've seen it happen in history or shape. I'll be far behind them
She's 80 years old, she's healthier than he ever was, but the fact that she depends on him as much as he depends on her, she's not going to last with him.
When a heart breaks, Psyche, when you're married to somebody for so long, Psyche, can I talk to my friend?
Can I talk?
I'm not being ignorant, I'm just saying can I talk to my friend, Psyche?
When a husband or a spouse loses their loved one they have to be a mayor for so many years
Their heart just breaks right in half and they're just like why even live anymore? Fuck this shit
I don't even want to eat breakfast or lunch or dinner anymore. I fucking white died and
Their heart just crumbles
But according to Kim, it's like oh, it's for cloud or something. What'd you say?
I'm just fucking around. It's like, yeah, I'm drunk as shit. I watched the whole football game with Aldi. Give me some
Disagreement that I'll have with Eminem. What about Eminem?
That is fair, you know
That's one of the things I hate about good times through these the lights fan, you're right
Like they're literally they're like you have the Giants
Another line
That's the bitch is the end of it. I mean you're talking I gotta put your camera be going to talk over everybody
And then you've got the fucking dead skins. Well, you know that good times now the commanders
Okay, who are in it? Who are the state capital of the state?
We are who are the
Sorry state capital of Maryland, but they want to have their own shit. So we keep your ass
Back up 95 and keep up that fucking in the 90s all right now I'm gonna say something psyche
Damn it. I was fucking good times. There's about good times and I love good times, but it was
What did the fucking say you maybe forget thank you, so
I know I'm mad like an asshole in your panel and this is not the way you like those your panels
We will show more respect. Please don't ban us kim. Let's actually show a little respect for psyche, please
I was not being ignorant.
Oh, good times, Pump Gasper, Chris Nova-Selig,
the base player for Nibbana.
Who'd you ever pump gasp for, Psyche?
Oh, Steve Airey from Journey.
Oh, Ben.
The lead singer from Hinder, I met Jane Hodder, who, as you know, plays Jason Borey.
And I've actually not met her, but I've spoken with her on a live panel, which I need to
I
Love you. So you thank you for letting us up here. I'm not leaving, but we will be quiet
I know we're trying to take we're not trying to take over your panel. She's just really aggravating the shit out of
my god, oh
My god, yo like who even says that I do I'll do you
You alright, buddy?
Where's that?
No, not the real God. No, not actual God. No, there's a live streamer named God that joins like his fellows.
Yo, did you see? Speaking of God, let's suck it off!
Speaking of the Godfather, I'm sorry. Speaking of the Godfather, did you see Robert DeMiro?
He walked out of Trump the other day.
Not him. She ain't no.
psyche i don't know if you know like i know you know donald trump is but him like
listen i could just aggravate kim by just being like donald trump's the best kim is like
fucking like visceral i'm right because you're a weirdo i despise a literal yo we're not talking
about politics i'll meet myself sorry i mean i'm muted us kim because we're not talking about
This is not your
Now you're gonna curse me out
Well, you're interrupting us
We are muted they can't hear us
We are we were muted oh shit
We are everything you're every every word I'm gonna say buddy
Go it's like where you said what you just every word
Go everybody are you guys okay? Are you fighting?
Perfectly fine Joe's an asshole if she keeps in a row to my friend site. She's not gonna be okay
Me that's my best friend. Yeah, I guess by your eyes are not fighting are you?
No, no, no, we're not fighting
We're not together we're friends
Kim is my friend for real. She's right. I thought she was your mom
Mommy
Mommy and I thought you were his stepdad sing or not sing psyche
Yeah, I was joking. I was joking. I was joking. I was joking. That was a joke
That's like he now that's too far Kim. No, she's like that was actually funny
I would have left harder, but she would have punched me in the eyes
So I didn't laugh as much, but thank you for saying that
So how long you staying mom? I mean Kim what did I say?
Well, say I just like watch YouTube like thank you for letting us up so like we're having fun
Like you don't even give a shout out to my best friend
So invasive she says you really do not understand the concept of personal space
Can I borrow your lighter for a cigarette, please is that too invasive?
Let's let's like talk. How's your uh Thursday going? It's like
Shut up. Can you you just over talk to me? Shut up. How's your Thursday going big dog? It's like
I'm not too bad. I'm just
looking at some uh
Double char with cheese. Look at some food like char burger with cheese. I will
Make you one big victim. I mean one day one day. Okay, then I come up always and you just let me from my mouth
And I just don't even ever give you no pennies
Not it not any back down tomorrow. You have two ninety nine
Two dollars and ninety nine. Thank you. Anything's appreciate everything's appreciate everything
I don't know how many things appreciate you.
Oh, and these things are $1.99, if anything's appreciated.
No, I'm fucking with you, Psyche.
You deserve, everybody should donate to Psyche.
He lets everybody up and all he does is get abused,
verbally abused the whole time.
Nobody ever lets Psyche talk.
Poor little Psyche never gets to give his opinions.
It's just blah, blah, blah.
Psyche's is just another little host, not me.
I love you, Psyche, you understand me?
I love you to show
Thank you. Yeah, there's sweethearts. I love you guys
Well, you just cost them out two seconds
Now you sound like beta you got somebody out then you love them two seconds later. Is that a beat impression knows that
It's a joke and that's what you do is about 24 seven jokes. Okay. Well, sometimes like
You want to be real you actually talked to somebody one-on-one
Like when I gave psyche memory, I played in chat the other day a co-word and I gave you myself a number in codes
You never you didn't get there. Yeah. I didn't get that. No, I did not get that
So you must not have got it. I hope I wish I bond upon you would get it. I wish she would send me a little text
Well, that's not me
No, she's not here
Well, thank you, Ash, bro, I'm just saying
I'm not showing Kim. I'm showing my coffee table. I don't want ashes
I don't think you should come to my house and as I stay out of my bubble like you're in my bubble right now
I'm smoking the cigarette not paying a damn thing attention. Oh, you're right. She's not our bubble guys don't know
Why nobody taught the Kim. She's just nobody. No, no, you cannot
like me on camera.
I didn't have the whole feel good today.
I haven't fucking did anything but sleep all day.
You wanna sit here and throw my face on camera.
Stop.
Okay, I won't show it again.
I didn't know you fucking started.
You did.
If you didn't write your fucking text message,
but you don't, it's not about me.
It's about you.
I don't read, I don't know how to read Spanish.
Kid, this is a joke.
Come on, come on, I'm fucking with you.
Kim, I apologize, okay?
Thank you.
Is that fair?
Yes.
It's a joke.
I mean, the first three times I show you didn't care.
Now, all of a sudden, it's the first thing.
All right, I'm gonna show you again.
But the last time I was showing my coffee table
that you flicked cigarette ashes on.
I didn't flick cigarette ashes.
Well, my cigarettes were literally still on my cigarettes.
Why is my vacuum cleaner full of cigarette ashes
every time you did?
Because you throw your cigarettes on the floor
when you're 12.
No, I don't throw my cigarettes on the floor.
I'm not good times.
You're drunk and you're mad.
Yo, let it be known I'm oh what's that noise?
No, that's your the one pardon the oven on that was your you preheat him off and go
You said you wanted to cook the pizza
You put the pizza in before it preheated. Oh, that's gonna be a doughy piece of shit
I'm still here. I just heard my camera off. This is embarrassing. Sorry guys. Sorry about this
Let me read the chat. Let me see who's in the chat. It's Marcy Fox in chat. You'll get your $200 tomorrow
Bulbas fall sack who would say that who would say bulbous balls
No, not you this guy Irby fatal said it you wrote bulbous sack. Yes, even row. Yes at the end like yes, Bob is sad
Oh my god, that pervy creep sweet peas here. Oh my god. No, I didn't say it. Herbie fatal said it
He just said it again. He just did it again
He just said
I'm just saying I'm just glad sweet peas here. She's a sweetheart
She's a sweet bitch
She's a sweet fucking
Extra innings yeah, I bet you wish you had extra innings
Thank you for lapping at me Goddy. I see Goddy's lol joke comment. Thank you, sir
Please Goddy laughs and a fucking joke
It's not done yet.
Oh, the pizza you put in the oven
and didn't even preheat, it's not done yet.
Yeah, I gotta talk to that.
I've been preheated, I mean, it was on.
It preheated when I went in there.
When I was one years old,
I used to like put pizza in my oven without preheating,
but now that I'm older and smarter,
I let the oven preheat.
Yo, I swear to God, I'm gonna smack you.
I did let it preheat.
I won't put you on camera.
Can we show the pizza when it comes out?
Oh, doughy and gay.
It's not gonna be doughy and gay, Joe.
I know how to cook I am a fucking female. I can smell it actually I smell the cheese
No, I actually can't smell it. You can't smell the pizza. Yeah, I can smell it. Yes, and I'll lie. I can smell it
Geez I got nostrils
What was the last time she went in Wednesday or you asking her extra ins or or the dog
Joe hates school on Mondays Wednesdays or Joe
I thought you said Joe drinks on Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays Joe hates me on Mondays with Yale. Yeah, you're good
Yes, thank you. Oh sweet big told me about an hour and a half to read that comment and get make it into my brain
But it worked
Somebody start a n-word tower for real like this is getting boring somebody in the chat. Let's pop his chat off. I
Walk after every meal. Come on. What do you think I'm a pig?
I'm here psyche. I'm just talking with you, buddy
I'm having fun with your chat man. Your chat's really cool and
cool
Thank you
What would you say to me? Okay, fuck your pizza
Start a G word tower. Thank you, Bulbas. Oh, Bulbas sack is here. Hold on
Somebody just made a comment about a Bulbas sack and now there's a guy in the stream named Bulbas sack
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say it's the same guy. I'm just gonna ruin you ruined it, Connie
Barbara
We're harvest sack like Barbara could almost be pronounced like Barbara's ball ball
All this ball this ball bra. I'm gonna get you Barbara. I don't know that's not
I have no idea you're scaring me though. We're moving
Are you living dead? Okay?
They might know that but she's scaring the fuck out of me
Well, it's a backwards and more tower. Yes backwards now
Dyslexic tower that's a dyslexic tower. That's what I love about Goddy. He has a little dyslexic. I gotta take a piss
I'm sorry come would you like a beer when I come back out?
Okay, would you like anything?
Game over man
Did he end the stream? Am I just talking to myself? Hello?
Shut Kim
Calm down
Hello
So always says ginger I see now if you could read it. No, I can't read the tower
But yeah, I do see it said ginger now. See thanks a lot, sweet pig. See that's why you're not sweet. You're evil P
Now she's named Sweet Pea, but she just called me a ginger that's racist
Why why do people not say ginger's racist? It actually is like a racist term show. Yeah, I am gonna show it
Goddy, I swear. I'm gonna show it soon. I'm not messing. I'm definitely showing that motherfucker. Hold on. Just give me a minute
Now I'm gonna show them your fucking undercooked pizza because you put in the oven
I didn't say you made the tower sweep you just had the you just had this you just had no we want to show a pizza
That's undercooked. It's not undercooked. Don't touch it. You're gonna burn your fingers off
Did that not just burn just touch a fucking oven. All right here look guys, honey
There you watch out
Oh, look, what's she doing? What is this? What is she doing, guys?
What the hell?
What the fuck? What are you doing?
I'm just asking. What are you doing?
Let it cook. What do you think I'm doing though? I don't want to know actually. I'm turning around to get the fuck.
It's an oven. Now oven eats every size. No, you don't understand. I want the fucking grown one on the cobblestone.
I'm not showing you. I'm not showing you. I'm showing the pizza.
I'm a real man that has oven mitts, like I might drink all the time psyche, but I'm a normal person. I have oven mitts in my house. I have like, like an oven and shit.
Jeez.
Oh, you stepped on that trash can.
No, that can be lower. Please step on step one step one. I got flip-flops on yeah
Are you walking up or not? All right, then fuck you
I'm talking to psyche what's up psych? How you doing buddy thirsty Thursday, man?
It's a third eye Thursday
thirsty
Remember third eye blind. I wish you would jump back from that. It's my fans
Remember it well
Imagine if I had red hair just hanging out of my head like yours. I'd be so fucking hot
Yeah, I mean I took the time to make a song for you psych not for you just for your show
You got to see clickin you got this clicking audio retard up here with some white trashy bitch
You fucks fake fucking black dudes, and you kick me off
When he's the you know, I know you're not talking about me
Members he pulled up that picture of that leg
Don't know
I mean he's he's out of her league and there's no way that fucking dudes banging cam like I wouldn't
But I'm not out here saying like I'm hot shit
You heard what she said. I literally didn't
Your audio sucks dick, bro. You're clicking like fucking
Your audio
You're unwatchable, dude
Yeah
Your voice sucks
Well, she's trying to do a deli pizza right now, so now you got me to talk to pal
All I'm saying is like
Took some time to make a song and he fucked wouldn't let me play it and he puts on this shitty ass AI
It's like
If you made a song and I don't know no no no no we're on we're on together and he just fucked me off and
Then they replaced it was a bullshit AI some bullshit AI that sounded real fucking stupid and he's just a hater
His name is random gay. His name is random gay guy. Like what? Really? Oh
First letter you three letters, dude, I mean you did something there. I'll give you that
That's good. I'm not saying anything wrong would be engaged. So my best friends are gay like psyche. Yeah, like so you don't have
You don't have to make your name random gay guy like come on be better than that. You want me to change it be bet random gay
Yeah, I do
Maybe cycle up a little faster a little faster on panel if I put it random gay
Change it the whole code
My way to sneak in huh?
Hogan was God. Yo, I swear to God Hogan was God
I know I might have said this earlier, but Kobe Bryant raped the woman and he when he died
Everybody's like, oh Kobe died
Joe shut up. Let me hear why she doesn't like him saying the M word. Oh, no, baby
Look, if he was being recorded when it said it, you'd be saying everybody said the M word
Let me hear what Kim has to say. Shut up, Joe
Bye, Kobe Bryant
Joe shut up. Let me hear
I swear to God I confused your breath on my arm when you yelled at me like that
Oh, I can hear the door open
The oven door so she's not my friend. She's using my oven right now, and I'm a dumbass and a retard keep calling me so
No, the shoe fits that so you're calling number shoes retarded you're calling me retarded shoes
What do you want random gay are you so I want to listen to Kim
All right, Kim. Come on. He wants to talk to you
Oh, he said she said how's it feel to one that she threw my silver on the ground. I could hear it
Come on he wants to talk to you come on well how's it feel to one she said twice
Here she comes come on cam for real thought of this gay guy random gay
Talk to him. Come on. The guy wants to talk to you. He likes you. He has crush on you
Say hi random guy. Say hi random guy. Hey
He said hi. Oh, there you go. Talk to him. Talk to her for real. What's up, Kim? How you doing Kim?
What's going on? So what happened? What's what's your beef with Paul Cogan? What's your beef?
I don't have a beef with Paul Cogan
I just don't like being disrespectful to the dead and Joe is a disrespectful asshole
Sinni you're talking about Kobe Bryant like that man didn't die with seven other children on board like
And that's beside the point. He's dead so fucking what?
It's been rude
All right random anything else you want or whatever any other things you need fucking weird
You can't put me on the spot man, I'm a free flower
Like I'm free
Literally playing my video game joy. Joe is just annoyed. What are you playing?
I'm pet wrecks pet rescue saga right now. I know what that is
I'd like you to tell me okay, so it's kind of like a Tetris game, but you actually have to um
You have to figure out the way to release the pet and rescue the pets and you got a
Clear all that it gives you a chance. You got a complete you do that on yourself
Keep your brain active. No, no, no my girlfriend does that too. She's always on her phone playing a little game all the time
You don't even have a girlfriend
They keep your mind sharp. Oh
My mind is so sharp. I'm I have multiple score system. My memory is
Yeah, so I try to keep my mind and start with games that actually make me think and use my brain to actually save your amount
Instead of like candy crush and all that shit like I play a screw master
a place for a master and
Pet recipe saga and I do love monopoly to go. I ain't gonna lie the gambler and he loves monopoly to go
I can have I can have a conversation with common folk because I'm a common folk. I'm just a fucking redneck
Yeah, we vibe well together. I mean, there's not there's not too much thought involved here. It's just a conversation. It's normal
Right
No, dude, if you could literally put me she said where are you from hillbilly?
Nowhere and just give me to my own devices I'll be happy
Actually, no, I would slaughter my own cows, my own chickens, my own pigs.
Oh, shit.
That's what I was going to do.
You cried when you saw a cow break its hoof.
You're not going to slaughter a cow.
Yeah.
If I had to do any of you, I would.
All right, go check on my oven.
Why is it beeping all day?
Sorry, I'm back big dog.
Thank you for talking to her for a minute, Ashley.
You calmed her down, to be honest.
I actually feel safe now.
She's actually calm.
There you go.
It's like he was about to cut the pizza. She had a knife in her hand
Then she looked at me with her eyes like and I was like whoa like please talk to her random cake
And why does it keep beeping?
Random gay is from the black. Oh the black tea sector. Oh, I get I get what you're saying bulbous ball sack
I get what you're saying bulbous. Oh, I see bulbous over all the time
God he said I fling my boogers while I take my morning shit. Well, that's kind of weird God
He you pick your nose and fling your boogers while you take a shit you fucking retard
No, he wants to talk to you Kim get back out here random gays in love with you
Yeah, he's not even gay anymore. He's actually heterosexual now that he talked to you. He loves you
Didn't turn me out. I really don't guys song again. Go ahead play it sweepy. What was it dmx?
No, it was just a rock song. It's all my dad. It's all my dex talk. It's all my dex talk
You do have a funny way of saying words
It was a joke
Come on, who's a joke?
But can you write in all upper cases again? You fucking creep. Thank you
Yeah, Joe
You know, no, no, I'm not talking to devil's eyes spanner banner, whatever it is. I don't care what it is get him out of here
No, because it's devil's eyes. Remember Michael Myers the blackest eye to devil's eyes
It's a fucking serial killer in chat. It's devil's eyes. I don't talk to murderers
Don't know Q actually. I don't know Q. I don't know. I mean, I know I'm on here
I've seen him on here. I've talked him on here, but I know he's from Pittsburgh. I don't know him
Personally, I don't know these things about you
I probably met an NA or an AA meeting, but who knows
This is a small circle of people when his girlfriend broke up with him on the anniversary
Listen to me his girlfriend broke up with him on the anniversary of the day his dad died like that is some heart
No, that is not him. I'm not lying. Did she do it on purpose that is fucked up
No, I see waited for that, but I hate you so much that I left. I was like
That's too far ball of a sack somebody being ball of a small sack, thank you
What are you doing out there?
Scrubbing bubbles. How do you do that?
He's got I did see his kid now, man, I did see his kid that is a nice kid
It didn't know let me say one thing about the Kings
I ain't gonna kiss no kittens ass. It looked a little scraggly. It looked a little scraggly
Who's he's got a kid and he found a kid, but it's like scraggly and dirty really
Yeah, I can relate to that
Hey Joe, I'm gonna tell you this dude beat his beat his cats look horrendous. I'm not gonna lie to you. Like
Let me talk random gay
Like Vita and I don't want to talk shit about her cats cuz I she was very nice to me
But Raven passed away, but I swear I've never seen we're cats than be this cat
They have like long ass weird hair
So you agree with me that's all right you agree with me I agree 100% I agree
It's just they look weird like a rich way. Yeah, fuck that
No, oh, that's my house
Let me hold the plate. I'll show that can I hold the plate literally gonna throw in your face
I can't even show them the plate
But they don't know what that piece
Oh, so you're gonna do not I see the pizza. Let me see the pizza, Joe. Let me see it
I would love to show it
I'm not gonna show it. Yeah, let me see it
I didn't know that was a team
Okay
The pizza looks good the pizza actually looks really good
Can I have a piece?
Let me have a piece of yours.
May I have a piece?
Oh, you're not going to give me a piece of my own pizza.
I cannot have a piece of my own pizza.
I can't even eat my own pizza, guys.
It's the way it works.
Don't threaten me.
Do not threaten me with a bottle.
Do not threaten me.
OK, you hear what I'm saying?
Do not fucking sit here and threaten me.
Hey, well, I can make you mad.
Do not sit here in front of me and promise me a minute.
OK, you're really making me.
All right, I won't talk about your pizza anymore.
It looks really good, though.
I'm not fucking with you.
It looks good.
Sorry, guys.
And she was holding a fucking bottle
and she's about to hit me in the fucking head with it.
Where are you going?
Fuck you.
Oh, and you know another thing.
I'm not showing her.
She's eating a pizza with a knife and a fork.
What a play.
Donald Trump with a knife and a fucking fork.
Who do you think she is?
Donald Trump.
She has a fortune knife in both of her hands the force in the left hand the nice. Yep Donald Trump. Don't do that
Oh my god, she just go bottle at me
Yeah, they already know that I've been
Hey
That's your business
I didn't know that pizza was your business. I was just trying to be funny
Okay, okay, I won't show it. I won't talk about pizza ever fuck again
Well, you're eating pizza I wanted to show the pizza
You know what we won't talk about anymore whatever you want to do
Thank you for letting me outside. I'm not leaving but thank you. So yeah, no, you know what don't talk to me on site
If you're not gonna be rude, thank you, psyche. I'm not leaving
Now Joe's I can smell
What did she vote for did she vote for Trump or no?
Well, no, well, we can't talk about her
Oh, she does want to talk. Okay
Amazon you can talk to them. Yeah, you know every time you okay miss, you know, I'm not trying to talk shit about her
She's literally sitting one foot away from me. I see hates Donald Trump so bad. Yo, she hates Trump so bad
I always aggravated like I voted for Trump and she literally just like it's so pissed off
Trump the range of a syndrome
Oh
History back to the people that wrote our independence and fucking wrote our declarations
Wow are right to fucking bear arms and
You must be 250 years
Basically trying to single-handedly destroy. No, he's not he just made he just made a great deal with Europe nations today a great trade
Thank you, Donald Trump
Thank you
Thank you, Donald. Well, they do it's all the goals kid. Where's the fucking
I wish that tattoo not my president or whatever the way you spell Trump. He could be your president
You could be a loser right along with them because if you stand or appreciate anything that man stands for
Then you're just a big loser. Oh, I stand for my president. I stand for my president, baby. I love you Donald Trump
You know morons that he's literally single-handedly
Starving as making no homeless are in love with
I'm gonna take some Iver Mekton right now put on let me take some Iver Mekton do this go every end of guy talk
Yeah, the random guys talking to you. Don't talk. Oh, yes. Yes, I'm dropped off. I think
Hey, what's up?
Don't talk. Let's like you have a time about hi Jojo
Jojo and that's too far
Mary and Jojo
Hi, sweetheart
What
What are you drinking psyche hell yeah cheers up brother
I'll crack a beer for my brother psyche right here. I'm gonna crack this for psyche
I have a couple
Let's calm down. Let's calm down. It shows like I have as I have tacos coming. I have tacos coming Doritos tacos locos
They're on the way. They're on the way. I was actually
Kim listen see you talk too much. He has the tacos being delivered from uber. He's not ate them yet
They're being delivered. Who's talking Joe? Oh psyche was
Have not stood up in the last five fucking minutes. Is that true? Is that true?
What's up? What's up? What's up?
Yeah, yeah, he had it ago. He had a run. He couldn't handle Kim. Yeah, she was like God, okay
The imagine being her best friend
No, Kim see that's a joke. She can't even take a joke right now
She's so pissed off because we said we voted for Donald Trump. She's so mad. She's eating her pizza like this like
It's like she's even playing it like she's mad like
Oh my god. It literally makes me want to vomit.
Well, why don't you go for a dog's house?
I have a signal.
Let me say one thing that we have let me say one thing that we're allowing treason to actively
Now may I say?
Okay, thank you. May I respond Kim? May I respond to what you just said?
Donald Trump made a great deal. She's starting to have to talk see how she can be off. She's so she hates Trump so bad
May I talk
May I talk? Let me get you to watch Fox News. I won't mute you. Let me get you to watch Fox News. May I talk? You watch Fox News? And I'm gonna rub you. Do you watch Fox News? It's not, it's not a question. Do you watch Fox News? Give me the, because if you do, they can't hear you. If you do, it's not real news.
Trump's dick. Today, Donald Trump made a historic deal with the European nations, a trademark
that is going to be, they will make the United States billions of dollars. So how about that?
No, he did. He's acting. Oh, yes, he did.
He's actually costing the American citizens trillions of dollars.
He's calling it a notch.
He literally just shut down all the clean energy and air windows and things that we have.
Shut down the windmills, not the windmills.
Oh my god.
And clean energy because he wants to pollute our fucking planet.
What are you? Can you really shut down the windmills? Not the windmills.
And all the loud people that are showing behind his back because they're not doing shit in America, because America wants to be too bad.
From the lay eggs to man is so done.
They're using billions of dollars on their own for their own nuclear fucking system straight with other countries, instead of doing what our presidents in the past have done.
Yeah, your enemies on a short lease. I like to keep going within their name. I make you president. You know everything
President yeah, well president will show their pizza
If you don't want to come on camera, no questions. No
100% what does that mean?
Oh, that means you're a hundred percent.
It's something below a hundred percent.
That means you're a hundred percent big.
It gave you a hundred percent discount on something.
What's that mean?
Oh, that means five-figured discount.
No, it means it's free, right?
That means that shoplifting.
A hundred percent off is free, right?
Talk to Psyche, man.
Sorry about her.
Psyche, I'm sorry about this.
I'm sorry about this.
A hundred percent off is free.
Yes, Kim.
This fucking moron tell her why he's not going to lower
the prices of prescription drugs more than a hundred percent.
He's going to list it below a million and ten billion.
Don't talk to me.
Don't touch me.
That cancer was gonna be a billionaire
and all the fucking pharmaceutical companies
are gonna be broke.
Don't touch me.
And I'm not saying that don't touch me.
Because you're the first one when I fucking you out. Don't fucking put your hands on me, you don't put your hands on me
You understand me? I literally poked you. I know you poked me. Don't do it again. No, don't do it again
Oh, she just did it again. I'm gonna say it like she's like Susan psyche. Listen, I've ever done Trump
I don't have a driver's license. No, I do have a driver's license. Come on psyche. What do you have in that psyche?
You're muted or you did something. Oh cheers up. What are you drinking brother? What are you drinking? It's like I
Haven't this
I can't hear me
Yeah, you would be drinking a fruity
Show that they're both nuts is pineapple coconut
You see it. Let me throw my camera off Kim. Do you see his cam?
I'd rather see Ferdy drinks than piss beer. Oh god
Is this mad?
It's all a smear and off. It's smear and off boys. There you go
Don't be showing it. He's showing it. It's like the spirit on pineapples
I apologize about her bro. She's just like in a mood right now. She's like a kind of attitude about Trump
The one thing I feel bad about is sometimes I call most like his paddle and then me and Kim are yelling and not one time
Do I even get the thanks like he for let me own his account?
Can I borrow your lighter, please? So I can see right tell you what there's a God in this guy
I'll kill that man quickly. Do you just hear what she just said? Did you do you would see what I mean?
Did you just hear that? That's it. That's a beanable fence can that could get like his channel banned
Yeah
You're done, you know, you're fucking done. No, you are
You're threatening on my channel, yeah, or you're threatening on my show
Listen, it's like you're like
Well, now you're gonna double up on the death threats. Yeah, geez you yeah
Hey
All right, can I ask you a question? No for multiple choice questions. Who's the most handsome psyche Johnny Depp Johnny Depp
Well Johnny Depp from Nightmare on part one Johnny Depp from Pirates Johnny Depp and psyche part two
Johnny Depp I say psyche part three Johnny Depp
Like he's like man, what the fuck is going on? See this is what I hate sucky that we're
She had a lot and she had lies just like you know to speak cuz she's on my panel you just like lie
But he's talking about Johnny that here
We're not gonna say like he's the sense of a shiny death though. I've turned the camera off
He's not sexy
I have
Across that me actually
Nobody kidnapped you you can fucking walk out the back door anytime you want
Yeah, you know what's weird psyche because I'm drinking she can throw pizza crust at me and throw bottles at me
And I can't do anything about it except I did I get arrested, but that's that's the way of women
That's the way of fucking women
Please don't do the justice that you're dessert you deserve
Okay, oh
Uh, try so you can't have none.
Get from Keaton another time.
Just help.
It's psyche.
If you never hear from me again after tonight, call the police.
He'll be at the bottom and he'll press the button.
What do you want?
Sure.
Whoa!
What the hell is that?
That looks like a harem.
Is that Colonel?
Is that the Colonel?
That's delicious right there. That's delicious.
Come on, it's not delicious. No, that's sexy. That is sexy, brother. Thank you for showing that.
That actually got me back. It actually straightened my mind out for getting pizza crust out of my head.
It actually made me think like, hell yeah, man. Hell yeah.
Did you see they're coming out with another naked gun? We're not talking to you anymore.
Yeah, I know they're coming out. Can you wipe the pizza sauce all by neck at least so I'm gonna sit here like an asshole
I've been on my fucking neck. You don't have to
Sike the other day I'm not gonna say the M word. I need you to hear me psyche
It was a joke like remember grave digger the monster shrunk recall grave digger. I
Said digger. It was it fucking
You love both Joe and Joe. Oh Joe. What did you say Joe? What do you what do you say?
What do you just say I?
Just heard I heard I thought I heard a word I
My my ears were perked wait. Did you say the word?
Guys, what do you say? What do you say tell me in the chat?
Do you say that he said the emmer right? Oh, yeah
He did okay
No, I said grave digger the monster truck drive. I'm like great. Oh, you never heard a great digger
Get the fuck out of here then really? Why does psyche have to stand up the pit or sit down the piss?
I meant I stand up. I stand up the
Can I issue a question Ken? Why does psyche have to stand up to take a shit like he's shit stand
I'm just kidding. It's a joke. It's a shitty joke. It's a really shitty thing backed up. Oh, he's backed up. All right
The gravity works my favorite
Thank you
No, they're saying I said David. Thank you
Where's the panel link? No, we're for you hurricane
Also page
Oh, it's evil Ron. Evil Ron McDonald is here. Mm-hmm. Where did he
start? Yeah, I'll be honest. Evil Ron McDonald, like a little emoji. Don't make
your evil. Say something evil. Evil Ron McDonald. You're not evil yet. You got
to say something really evil. I mean, you just can't make your name. Oh, sweet
Let me see who's coming up
Okay. Yeah, I'm waiting for my where's my food. I'm so hungry. I'm I'm rich my food. I need two coffees and like three tacos
I remember like an hour ago, you said you ordered tacos and it's fucked up like where the fucks the delivery
I'm a custom out brother. All right, Kim. It's not your bad. It says Alberto is approaching. Hold on. Let me check it
It's approaching
We're in your backyard
That was good timing
They're in your back yard psyche. Come to your back door. We have your tacos
Maybe I'm sleeping. I hope you have a nice breast of night or a nice night of rest either way one of the other
Prairie I made not reading that out loud. I
Mean he's basically here. He's like outside. He's like almost here. They got far away
Well walk outside and meet him. He's not going to walk up into your walk outside so you don't know your address. Oh
There he is he's walking I can see him
What did you order big dogs and tacos and what else any other sides
Three tacos two coffees and I have one beer left. I finished these ones. Yeah
That's why I love music two coffees on top of the tacos. All right. I want you to hear this
You can't play music
Okay, well, I mean if it's like her song Joe, I think it's fine
But if it's her song like but if it's not if it's like a famous song, then I can't play it
No, she's having a song and I but I'm not listening to songs. I'll be back in one sec
Yeah, is it good? I mean, it's a good song. I want to hear I mean, I love a good song
You so much in meow my lawn. Oh my
Like
Shooting and say it's like he's happy me. What people run my dog. What?
Terrible I
Don't know. I think the food's almost here. I mean see let me see that look at it
You know the Doritos Locos Tacos are like the best tacos actually. Oh, it was dropped off. It said, okay
Come back Joe you have Mac is fine
Sure, she's not just behaving
She didn't like that I said the Nellie song like I love you. I love you, baby. I love you
my little sweetie. That's the song Nellie. Yeah I do. You want to bet? Yeah I do. Look
I love you.
First of all,
Baby,
the song that I was playing for you
was baby.
It's four things.
Love you.
That's the fucking one.
I do.
I'm going for it.
Baby,
I love you.
Before me,
buy my work.
Everything about YouTube.
It was literally.
Swiping away with my boo.
That's not the song I was playing. Yeah, but we don't care what you're playing. This is what I was playing. We're not playing some music on me.
Yeah, Taco Bell. How fast will I inhale these tacos? This is a question.
They look good, Suggie.
Eat it, eat it, even sexier.
Shovel it right up your gullet.
There we go, nice.
Every crumb, don't even miss a crumb.
Hello, I'm sorry. Was this really there? I forgot. Hold on cold. Oh, this is hot
Give me a hot coffee guys hot and cold
Mmm, so good
The tricks
It's in a blend coffee. That's the way it won.
Oh, it says, you know where we're at. Well, thank you, guys.
I'm really hungry.
See the skinny person eat?
Would you like me to drink this coffee? Here you go, Pangey. Come on up, sweetheart.
We'll get a pinch.
Oh, this is good, Bill, guys.
I got a couple of copies.
She's not going to walk up for me, but can I please
light the blunt?
Can I light the blunt for Suggie?
Give me that blunt right now and I'll light her.
Give me the blunt.
You want me to light the blunt?
No, I want to light that fucking blunt.
You want to light my blunt?
No.
Give me the blunt.
Because you always tell people I steal your weed.
You want to light my blunt?
I'm not doing this on my best friends panel about doing this. Yeah, give me about you, right?
No, I can't let it you got a lady. Oh, and you're gonna burp on it. Oh
Why you got like you already struck a cigarette. Give me the fucking one. Thank you. So I give this for you, brother
I'm gonna do a French in nails. You can see you go up my nostrils
There it goes, right up to the brain.
I'm insane in the membranes.
Oh, sorry, Kim.
I said membrane.
Are you a fucking pork chop out of me?
But I'm saying.
What's up, dude?
How are you?
Hey, babe.
Here's my little baby kitty cat here.
Let's see tricks.
Oh, look at this cat Kim. Look at this cat. Come on. She's like these cats very cute. You didn't even look at it. I've seen her. You didn't even look at it. I've seen this cat.
I want to do Joe. I actually have a pretty good memory. Do you? Yeah. I don't think you know, but I really want to brush eyes when I'm drawing. Oh, that is so cute. So I get that little cat. I want to show you the cat, Kim. You don't want to be on camera.
I have five cats. She's in this one. It's right. No, it's not gray. It's white and brown
Look at this little belly cover
Look at him. Look at him. He loves it. Oh, you like being pet like that. Look at his peck tortoise
Hey, we have a guest welcome hurricane park welcome hurricane park
You're welcome. You're welcome.
Hurricane Para.
Hello.
What up?
Hurricane.
It's hurricane. Okay. Are you cool?
You're cool. You're not going to pour bomb, are you?
You won.
You're like a hot guy. Hold on.
Look at this guy.
You see him? Hold on.
Oh, that's great. Wow great with a jacks teller. Oh, oh, that's your girlfriend
nah, fucker
She threw me out of the book. She threw me out of the bus. So
Yeah, I just finding myself a new home. I guess
Where you from you sound from Africa now from the Virgin Islands
Okay, are you black or white black?
Hold on hold on aprocurbia
African no, I'm gonna walk up story Kim because I gotta walk up with her because she don't want to walk back
Okay, so I'm gonna get by Joe
Bye Joe. Thank you. Bye. You and brother. I can see the game born in the watch every glasses
Good night, okay, so hurricane para you know, you're home. Oh, this is you. Oh my gosh. Hold this guy
Yeah
That's you
Good looking you're looking good looking too. How'd you find my show?
You know sends on the day that I came to
Your show like I find I saw you on my notifications and I just press on it
Okay
Meet me prayer page
Nice to meet you you do
But yeah, um, I came here to ask you site. Do you know who Shannon Shannon is Shannon Maro?
Shannon Shannon who?
Shannon Maro Shannon is my name. Oh
Your name is Shannon. Okay. You have a you it's a kind of is a female name in the United States
But I like it's a kind of masculine when it's on them
a good looking guy like
like masculine names and guys
it's kind of cool when guys have
masculine names
I do, I like it
yeah, nothing wrong with it
yeah, but her is the problem
that's why I'm now here
to see if she's gonna pull up here because
Bita knows who she is
okay, Shannon
so you know Bita, you found me through Bita
or what's going on?
No, no, no, it's just um, I wanted to ask beta about um, what happened between her and Shannon because now I'm involved because
After what I found out about Shannon now, I'm calling her after along with um her her new white knight
Name captain fuckable. I'm calling. I'm calling both of them out and I and I hope they're watching this, too
This is probably not the place to do that
Go five five be go five be it on her show and ask her about that there
Hey, she she's bad. So
Then you know, this isn't the place for that though, you know, we're all trying to hang
Yeah
Come back in a few minutes. I'm back in a few minutes. Okay. I want to just talk to Paige for a minute
Hey Paige, how are you sweetheart? I'm all right. How are you cuz everybody doing hi chat? What's up?
Okay, I have in my you like these page. Look at these Doritos Locos tacos. They're they're in an actual Doritos show
That's that's dope. Yeah, that is that's a good
Have that here. I've got some I got like some
treedos in my bag my golf bag
Nothing cool like that
You're good. How have you been?
I've been alright. I've just been working and there's another one smoking balls just crack honestly tonight
I fucking I have so many. I'm sorry. I'm really excited to be swear like I always swear like a trucker
Well, I'm apologizing for okay, seriously. I've gotten so good at I'm so good at me today and yesterday
We're like golden days. I can draw got my my two buddies today one buddy today and one buddy yesterday, I guess
Pretty good on the golf cart on the golf cart. Yeah on the golf course. Yeah, I'm killing it out there
I blew my own mind today because I was like are you looking for my ball and looking for all these balls so close and I'm like
That's my fucking ball. That's my fucking ball. I'm just so excited. It's doing good. I'm doing really good
Well, and how's your show going? I heard like a rumor your time off, but I was hoping it wasn't true
Are you uh, are you good on your show? Don't want to say in my chat. They're like, oh, she's taking out your break
I was like, oh, I hope not. Like I was worried that you got like
Okay
To hear off I'll do lose it all my subscribers that I might fat like not I just wouldn't I can't do that. I got
You can't do that to people you got to keep
Yeah, someone's starting rumors so yeah, it's like high school all over again
And I was like in high school in a high school. I actually was like
Not that popular 9th and 10th grade, but I was like doing my own thing and then 11th to 12th grade
I kind of got accepted by my class. We had a really small class and they I got all the parties and stuff. Yeah
Time, let's see
Fucking favorite thing to do everybody I'm not even that special
How'd you show my glory though? Have you wouldn't the last time you went on?
Well yesterday when I was golfing and then I did I did it fucking like four hour reading
Before I came golfing and then yeah
I mean I've been doing it. It's like look it. Okay, so I couldn't find them for a while that can't I'm not gonna use them on my
Channel, but like I've had these for a long long time
It's not a big deal.
You seen it before?
I'm trying to get this dollar to come on here.
No!
They're pretty cool.
Actually, I gotta show you these cards.
I gotta show you these cards.
You gotta look.
The only thing is, okay, with them, when I bought them like a long time ago, and I don't
use them, I can't because, look it, I spent so much money on them, I fucking hate this.
Yeah, there are two thin little bit then they are there and I yeah, I'm I'm angry about it
So do you like do I make a collage out of them or laminate them or something? What can I do with them?
I'm eating decks on Timo and they're all the busy
And I know that guy
His name is Kyle his skateboarder
Look at the four of wands in this deck like this is I gotta show them to you guys. These are way too cool
Let's try it. It's good stuff in his piehole. I love it. Look at the magician gangsta
Probably know that guy too
They're just really cool like they're just really cool
They would be like good dad and all they would be good
Good. I don't know. They're just different. They'd be good. Maybe I don't like them. Yeah, I like them artwork on them
It's pretty incredible. I'll just show you like look at the hangman. This is probably one of my favorites checker
The shipper the shipper pole. She's all cleaned up and hanging it's a hangman. Oh, yeah
I don't know, but yeah, so how's things with you?
Well, I'm pretty good. It's like yesterday was a lot of drama. I would say it was like I wasn't really trying to go for the drama
but you know how it goes.
It happens.
I think we have days that are better than others, you know. Sometimes it's, okay, we're getting asked to you or sometimes you're not, you know?
Well, did you know that? You know what the ghost did, right?
No.
Goes donated about five hundred dollars last week
Last night I said what are you channel for fucking sale he owns it now because you're not for sale
I'm not and it's like and I still like we'll run it, but
He has some like kicks. He has some kicks to go. He has some
Sponsored panels. I'm gonna be able to buy a computer now
You know, this is like my best month on YouTube over a thousand dollars on YouTube this month
My first my first month over
But it doesn't did it did it come did it come with good morals?
It came with like, you know treat the channel to the channel well
And it's like that's just the monetized part of it. That's that's like the monetized part of it
You know, it's like and then plus I get
The lovers, what is that? What is that?
Drink yeah, I like that string
She lost her fucking mind and shaved her head
I remember it was
It was because I think she was gonna get a drug tip a hair test
I was just saying when I'm having a mental breakdown. I'm like fucking I'm going Britney Spears 2007 to 2009
Yeah, I mean it was it was an interesting time
It's a real fortune going through difficulty, right? He's crazy, but it's okay. I think that's what happens when you
She's had a hard life
Fame fame is not everything is chalked up to me, you know
Well, I agree and it's like when you're
Mickey Mouse Club
Yeah, the Mickey Mouse Club and it was like a ten-year-old probably
Well, like even look what happened to Drew Barrymore is the same thing she fucking
I was like look it looks like you if you had crown of thorns on your head and stuff
Yeah, bro, I like it
Isn't it cool with that?
But um, you know, that's the thing
Oh, look at the 10 of coins, this is a little risky
I don't know, I don't get in trouble, it's not like poor mommy will
That's good
They're all like, I'm trying not to show you a case
So this is the, look, that was a little scary
That's a fucking justice card
Yeah, we would lose our mind too and you know, when day when you're super famous, I'll fucking find you do and tick tocks and dancing around with knives.
Or me.
I started doing TikTok's page and it's like it's a whole different audience on YouTube
I know what TikTok's all about, like I actually when I started my YouTube channel, I did have
TikTok and I blew up on TikTok and it was overwhelming and it was easier to become famous
on TikTok than it was here for sure, that's not famous but you know what I mean to like
actually get known to like whatever, be a big, yeah I was monetized on TikTok in three days
and three days I was able to start a membership program
We had so I think she's talking is the way to go home. I think we lost my lost page
We have the Tom flash is backstage stroking his dick
You will not be led on the show, but a random guy is led on the show. Yo, what's up, dude? How you doing? Hey?
Amazing page
My guy my guy listen. I made you a nicer song
I know that you like those little AI songs, okay?
And you like to like talk about what you do on your channel
So I made you something real real short real nice. Can I at least play it?
Sure, but it'll be insulting and I'm sure it will not be I won't like it, but go ahead play it. It'll be fine. Okay. Here we go
I
That's all okay. Well, I let you play the whole thing
It call me F a ggot in that. Oh, no, no, no, no
Is that you a uf and F a ggot? No, no, I didn't say that
You didn't say that okay. No, I heard that. No, okay. Yeah, I guess I miss her. I miss her. You miss her
It's an artistic expression. I
Think I think my AI better than that. It's not though. Yeah, I mean I cook that up in like what?
four minutes
It's like these fish tacos all day long, and then it says you effin effing
No, it's probably
Did you take ivermectin today? That's probably what it is don't stop saying that I
Mean come on Jesus Christ. I mean they don't say that word. I want to hear about any kind of
medications, okay, I
Do not give medical advice on the show
Okay guys I have one more coffee one more taco and one more beer left
We shall see what happens tonight
I'm not eating the tacos. I was eating the tomatoes for the sec. I was eating the tomatoes
Okay
Pretty good though I chew it in already I have one more left. Yep
Let's take this one out.
Close the way.
Oh, fall asleep.
Or stay on for a lot longer.
We'll see what happens.
What do I have in here?
Do I have some sauce?
Did he mean one sauce?
Not one sauce.
OK.
OK, if they're on that away.
I should have a friend coming over
if I don't have my friend coming over.
I'm just going to fall asleep.
Okay.
How are you guys doing tonight though?
Let's do a
Little giveaway
Where's Joker been
Anyone see Joker around can someone match me on this
Shamrock BNC. Congratulations. You just want a free membership on psyche awakens channel
Hopefully they enjoy their membership guys I have everything beyond the paywall. I have over like a thousand hours of shows
You guys like this show you'll love the membership promise you
Here's guys, I got my final heart or laminae
Hey grammar, we're in that work
I have one more coffee left, one more beer left, and one more taco left. Plenty of, plenty of
weed.
Hey Vicky, how are you? I don't mind Vicky, but I'm a little bit too drunk right now,
He's very cool
Vicky hung on my tiktok Vicky saw my tiktok
You guys want to watch my tiktok? I'll go after this show. I'll go do a quick tiktok. I
Do really quick readings on there a little bit too drunk to it right now. I need to drink this coffee smoke this cigar figure it I
Can't smoke on tiktok. It'll restrict my channel immediately
I need a mod to stay turnt. Well, that's you stay turnt saying that. I can't really
Listen to the person saying it
This is a
Cinnabun flavor coffee, it's really good
Really good. I need to stay turnt. Well, stay turnt's a good guy. I don't mind stay turnt really
I'm going to put away these things that I've already had.
That gets thrown away, this gets thrown away.
This gets thrown away.
This one is fine.
OK, that gets thrown away.
And this one.
So I just have the two left over.
Uh-oh. It spilled it everywhere. Okay, shit.
Okay, guys.
That's everyone doing I guess I'm gonna go over it since there's 22 people here. You can look like it
Go go check out my take talk guys. You can go say hi to me over there. Okay. I'll do a reading for if you want
I'll come back here later
Yeah, your song wasn't very good
Okay, there's my take talk guys go over there go see me over there. Okay, I'll be ready. I'll be right there
Love you. Thank you